PART.1: You want to start?
PART.2: All right, you can.
PART.1: Ok, I'm going to start.
PART.1: One, two, three...
PART.2: Go!
PART.1: No?
PART.2: The chair?
PART.1: Wait, wait, wait...
PART.2: So there's no green bottle
and I think it's fine.
PART.1: Do you think it is really?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Because I am not 100% sure.
PART.2: So you keep the card.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.2: It is yours.
PART.1: Maybe we do it wrong,
you know?
PART.1: I guess is not the point.
PART.2: This?
PART.1: Ah! You are right!
You are right!
PART.1: Let's go, let's go for this.
PART.2: Bottle, white, book.
PART.2: Yes, yes, yes.
PART.2: You keep it.
PART.1: If we both think
it is the right answer
then it is going to be
the right answer.
PART.2: Green, chair, blue, book.
PART.1: I think you are good
at spotting the right ones!
PART.2: The right ones?
PART.1: I think you are good
at spotting the right ones!
PART.2: The right ones?
PART.1: I am good at spotting
the ones that are not.
PART.2: Yes, I see a card there.
PART.1: Yes, yes, yes.
PART.2: Is the same, yes?
It's always the right one.
PART.1: You always get the blue book,
oh my God!
You always get the blue book.
PART.2: Is the same, yes?
It's always the right one.
PART.1: You always get the blue book,
oh my God! You always get the blue book.
PART.1: Yes, I accept it.
PART.2: This?
PART.2: Ah, no! Yes, yes, yes!
It's true, it's true.
PART.1: You are right.
PART.1: Yes, I think so, you.
PART.2: Why do you always get
the blue book ones?
PART.1: You are just lucky enough
for the blue book, oh my God!
PART.1: There is no white in this picture
and the grey is the mouse.
PART.2: Yes, you are right
so you win.
PART.1: But there's no blue,
yes, there is.
PART.2: Yes, you are right
so you win.
PART.1: But there's no blue,
yes, there is.
PART.1: Ok, I am right, I am right.
PART.2: Is it your turn?
PART.1: No, I think it's your turn.
PART.1: Ok, take it, take it.
PART.1: Yes, I think
that is the right answer.
PART.2: There is the grey and the mouse.
PART.1: Yes, yes,
because there is no blue in this
and there is no book in this.
PART.1: Last one...
PART.1: Yes, you are right.
PART.2: Right?
PART.2: There is no white
and there is no ghost.
PART.1: I think you won.
PART.1: Yes, you won
because I have four and you five.
PART.2: One, two, three...
PART.1: Yes, you won
because I have four and you five.
PART.2: One, two, three...
PART.1: Six? What?
How many do you have?
PART.1: Are you sure
some of those
are not from the training session?
PART.1: How do you have seven?
PART.2: I think I've got the most
of the blue books.
PART.1: I think you've got
all the blue books.
PART.2: Yes, the three blue books
were for free.
PART.1: Yes, I think you just won
for the blue books.
PART.1: Actually a friend of mine
has this game
and she told me several times to play it.
PART.1: It's like fun
because it's like so stressful
PART.1: because you have to pay attention
and so on.
PART.2: The odd one is the most tricky.
PART.1: Once you play it a bit
you have to kind of remember
a bit the answers
when you get used to it.
PART.2: The odd one is the most tricky.
PART.1: Once you play it a bit
you have to kind of remember
a bit the answers
when you get used to it.
PART.1: But I have never tried this game.
PART.2: We should play
more games like this,
we could buy this for the camping.
PART.1: Yes, actually I have to ask them
if they want to come.
PART.2: Who?
PART.1: This friend of mine
is Hungarian and also her boyfriend.
PART.1: Yes, I should probably
ask them as well.
PART.1: Yes, this is really fun
because it doesn't take much space.
PART.2: Is it for two people only
or it can be played by many more?
PART.1: No, I think more
and the most stressful it gets
the more people that are.
PART.2: Is it for two people only
or it can be played by many more?
PART.1: No, I think more
and the most stressful it gets
the more people that are.
PART.2: It would be more fast.
SUPERVISOR: How was it?