PART.2: Okay, do you wanna start? Or should I start?
PART.1: Should we do...?
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: Okay.
PART.2: 1, 2, 3, go... And once, only.
PART.1: 1, 2, 3 and then go?
PART.2: 1, 2, 3 and then, go.
PART.1: Okay, once.
PART.2: Only one time.
PART.1: Rock, paper, scissors, go!
PART.2: 1, 2, 3, go!
PART.2: Oh, I thought 1, 2, 3, go!
PART.1: Rock, paper, scissors, go!
PART.2: Okay, sorry.
PART.1: Okay?
PART.2: Yes, sorry.
PART.2: Rock, paper, scissors, go!
PART.1: We did it three times... Ah, because we... Smart!
PART.2: Yeah, so, you start.
PART.1: Okay, ah...
PART.2: Know you're now an animal, keep that in mind.
PART.1: Am I an animal to keep in the house?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Okay.
PART.2: Am I an animal to keep in the house?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: Is it possible to keep it in the house?
PART.1: Yeah!
PART.2: Okay. Okay.
PART.1: You... Are you allowed to do it again if you said yes?
PART.2: Let's just do like me, you, me, you, and that's it. And we're five and five.
PART.1: Okay, am....
PART.1: Am I... Do I have...Do I stand on four legs?
PART.2: Yes, you do.
PART.2: Em...
PART.2: Okay.
PART.2: Am I like an unusual thing to keep in your house?
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: Am I fluffy?
PART.2: I mean... Not really.
PART.2: I mean, you have fluf, but you're not like a fluffy animal, like it's not on the fluf that you have, but, like, it has fluf.
PART.2: Like, it has... Like, when you touch it, it's not, hard, or something, it is fluffy, but it's not like a fluffy animal, that you say: "Oh! A fluf ball!", or something. Okay.
PART.1: Okay, okay, okay.
PART.1: Okay.
PART.2: So, I'm an unusual thing... Am I like... Okay, I wanna say "dangerous", but like, do I have the fame of being a dangerous animal?
PART.1: No, not specifically, there're different types, but no.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: Am... Do I personally, as Emma, love this animal?
PART.2: I mean, you probably do, they're really cool. I don't remember you telling me... Like, from the animals you love, it's none of them, like, the staples, you know?
PART.1: Okay, okay.
PART.2: But you probably like them too.
PART.1: So, it's no pig.
PART.2: No, it's not a pig, sadly.
PART.2: Okay, so...
PART.2: What was... What were my questions again? I'm... I can be kept in a house, I'm not usual to be kept in a house, and I'm not necessarily dangerous.
PART.1: You are...
PART.2: Am... Do I stand on four legs?
PART.1: Mmm...
PART.1: Difficult. Ye...
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: Mmmm...
PART.2: Sometimes. Like, it's not the normal thing.
PART.1: It is, but... It's kind of difficult, but yeah, four...
PART.2: The animalitself has four... Like, four extremities, like not four legs, but like, four things... Okay.
PART.1: Yes, yes, yes, yes.
PART.2: That was my fourth question.
PART.1: Am... Is... The animal that I have on my head, is it bigger than I am?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: For sure!
PART.2: For sure, yeah, yeah. It is a big animal.
PART.1: Okay.
PART.2: Am...
PART.1: That was the fifth, right?
PART.1: I think it was the fifth, now...
PART.2: Did you start, or did I start?
PART.2: You started, right?
PART.1: I started, yeah.
PART.2: Then, that's the fifth, yeah.
PART.2: Okay, my fifth is...
PART.2: I'm so confused. Am...
PART.2: Am I...?
PART.2: Like, you said there's different types... Do these types dif... Like, are they really different from each other? Like, the types of thing, animal?
PART.1: It can.
PART.2: It can be very different, but they're all the same animal.
PART.1: I mean, what do you mean with very, very different?
PART.2: For example, dogs, they're all dogs, but like, they can be really different if they're like one class or another.
PART.1: Ah, yeah, of course, it can be, yeah.
PART.2: Yes? Okay, okay.
PART.1: Am... Am I someone that I would find on a..., on the... on the normal... How do you say? Am... A normal farm?
PART.2: No. A farm?
PART.2: No, you're not.
PART.1: Like a...
PART.2: You're not. Okay.
PART.2: Am I an animal that lives in hot climates?
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.2: Yeah?
PART.1: Well... No... No.
PART.2: Yeah or no?
PART.1: No. I'm thinking.
PART.2: Or maybe they live in both climates?
PART.1: Yeah, I'm not quite sure actually, I think probably both.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.2: Okay, I don't think ten questions is enough.
PART.1: I'm...
PART.1: Am...
PART.2: Think big. Like, don't th... I mean, don't think big animal, but like think, expand your thoughts, don't think only in Europe, think like the  world.
PART.1: Oh, do they have huge ears?
PART.2: Not really.
PART.1: Oh, it's not an elephant.
PART.2: I didn't... That's why I said not big animal but think like the world, because you're not gonna find this... Okay.
PART.2: You didn't ask the question, so, whatever.
PART.2: Am...
PART.2: Okay, so, I live in both climates, I can be kept in a house...
PART.2: But it's very unlikely, I have four legs, almost...
PART.2: And... What else did I say?
PART.1: Ah... Unusual to keep in the house...
PART.2: And if I live... No.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: Am...
PART.2: Am I an animal that you know that Sam likes? That I like?
PART.2: Have I ever talked about this animal?
PART.1: Mmm... I'm not very sure actually.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: It could be that either very much or that you not at all like that animal that you are right now.
PART.1: Am...
PART.1: Am I an animal that actually exists nowadays?
PART.2: Yes, yes.
PART.1: Okay.
PART.1: How many have... We have nine, eight...
PART.2: I have seven, you have eight.
PART.1: Okay, that's...
PART.2: And this is my eighth.
PART.2: Am...
PART.2: I really don't fucking know.
PART.2: Am I a big animal?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: I'm like, small.
PART.1: Mmm.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: Uff...
PART.1: Am I a tourist animal?
PART.2: Tourist animal?
PART.1: Like... Like...
PART.1: From... The region that I am from, when people go there, is it like a standard thing to go visit these animals, or like...?
PART.2: Oh, yeah.
PART.2: Yes, yes, you are an attraction.
PART.1: Ah! Aha! Mmmm, okay.
PART.2: Okay?
PART.1: Mmmm.
PART.2: Okay. Ehm...
PART.2: Am I... Like, do I make babies by laying eggs?
PART.1: Eh... Ah! What... What the fuck?
PART.2: You don't know?
PART.1: Eh, you do.
PART.2: I do?
PART.1: You lay.
PART.2: I lay eggs, perfect.
PART.2: Okay, your turn.
PART.1: Ahm...
PART.1: Can I already start guessing?
PART.2: Yeah, of course.
PART.1: Am I a camel?
PART.2: Yes, you are a camel!
PART.1: I'm a camel!
PART.2: You're a camel!
PART.1: Okay, nice!
PART.2: I still have one question, though.
PART.2: Okay, so, I lay eggs, I'm unusual to keep in a house, I'm a small animal...
PART.2: I'm not dangerous, but there is a chance that some of...
PART.2: My... like my...
PART.2: I mean, I'm not specifically dangerous, but I can be dangerous... That's what you meant, right?
PART.2: Or there are some types that are dangerous?
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: I mean, don't think big dangerous. Don't think big dangerous.
PART.2: Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
PART.2: Am I like... How do you say it?
PART.2: Am I a type of bird?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.2: Those were my ten questions. He said I could have an extra question.
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.2: So, I'm not a bird. Am I a reptile?
PART.2: Am I a snake?
PART.1: No. No, you... Sorry, you're not... No, no, sorry.
PART.2: I'm not a reptile? Okay. Then...
PART.2: I'm not a reptile...
PART.2: And I lay eggs, and I'm not a bird...
PART.2: What else lays eggs?
PART.1: I mean, mmm, ah...
PART.2: You know what I mean with reptile?
PART.1: Yeah...
PART.2: Like...
PART.1: Rightig, but, don't think like... Okay, look, don't think if I say eggs, don't think like eggs, like, you know, like actual eggs that you, like, always see...
PART.2: Am I a frog?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Ah! Okay, I get it. I get everything now.
PART.1: K-ching!
PART.2: Because of the poison, an everything, I guess, right?
PART.1: Exactly, yeah.
PART.1: I wanna see how mine looks like.
PART.2: Ah, beautiful!
PART.1: Oh, mine is so cute! Hey, baby! These are the ones that spit, right?
PART.2: Yeah. No! Those are llamas.
PART.1: Mm, true.
PART.2: These ones are the camels.
PART.1: Nice. Javi?
PART.2: Javi!