PART.2: So we can discuss on tomorrow meeting.
PART.1: Tomorrow meeting,
we can advance now, yes.
PART.2: Why not?
PART.1: It could be,
now, the point is when the people
don't know each other,
it is supossed to make questions
to say how are you?
Which are you hobbies?
Whatever, whatever, whatever.
PART.2: I am not very good at that.
PART.1: No, but anyway,
it is not our case.
PART.1: When we know each other,
we can comment any other stuff.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: I think, I don't know,
but to me is always a problem
to start conversations.
PART.1: Yes? Really?
PART.2: Yes, I don't know.
PART.1: But it depends on
how much you know the other person.
PART.2: In English, it is my problem,
but in my language, no.
PART.1: Yes, it happens the same to me.
PART.2: Because sometimes I feel that maybe
I say something wrong in English,
because my English it's not perfect.
PART.2: I don't know how to start the chat
but in my language I think I am good.
PART.1: Yes, the same here.
PART.1: It is also something
because of our personality, I think.
PART.1: You don't want to do something
if you feel that it's not going to be ok.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: About what can we talk,
have you sleep finally
three hours today or not?
PART.2: Yes, five hours.
PART.2: Really?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Which part?
PART.1: The document.
PART.2: No, which part you changed?
PART.1: Only a five with a six.
PART.2: With...?
PART.1: Because I thought you were including
five in SP images,
five in PII images
and you included six and five.
PART.2: But it was five.
PART.1: No.
PART.2: Yes, it was five and five.
PART.1: No, six and five.
PART.1: I reviwed it three times
and I was counting one,
two, three, four, five and six.
PART.1: Then one, two, three, four, five.
PART.2: No, I don't think so.
PART.1: Yes, I am pretty sure.
PART.1: Do you want to check?
Check in your mobile.
PART.2: Yes, let's check,
it's strange.
PART.1: If we need to resume it again
we can't.
PART.1: It closed.
PART.1: But I was checking and the six,
the other one you included...
PART.2: So, at the end,
it's eleven images you say?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Really?
PART.1: Do you have access here?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: I think you included one
that I did not comment
but was a good one.
PART.2: That's strange.
PART.2: Maybe I was tired, I don't know.
PART.1: Or maybe I was sleepy
when I saw the figure.
PART.2: Let's check what...
PART.2: A bottle, yes.
PART.1: Otro bostezo.
PART.2: It's not responding.
PART.1: To be anotated.
PART.2: It's not working.
PART.1: Ok, you can check it later.
PART.1: But I'm pretty sure
you included six not five.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: Ok, so tomorrow we don't meet.
PART.1: Which are your plans?
Let's talk about something...
PART.1: What do you want to do next weeks
with your free time?
PART.2: If I have...
PART.1: If, yes,
I suposse a little bit, maybe?
PART.2: For next week
I have three papers to review,
two leaves.
PART.2: Javier Roca sent me a paper
from CBC.
PART.1: About what?
PART.2: Action recognition.
PART.1: Ah, from a journal?
PART.2: Yes, yes, I accepted.
PART.2: I have to review it plus two nips.
PART.1: Ok, but when you have free time,
what do you want to do
with your wife in your free time?
PART.2: In the free time...
PART.2: My free time is just in the weekend.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: This is my regular free time plan.
PART.2: On Saturday morning we go shopping
for the whole week.
PART.2: In the afternoon, a little bit sleeping.
PART.1: Nice.
PART.2: And then we go a little bit walking.
PART.2: Sometimes we come to Barcelona
and walk, drink something,
Coca or some coffee
or we walk around.
PART.1: But you don't like coffee or Coca.
PART.2: It is not a matter of liking,
I cannot digest it.
PART.2: But Coca is better,
but I still have the same problem.
PART.1: Ok, yes.
PART.2: Then we look TV series or movies.
PART.1: Which kind? Which kind?
PART.1: Horror?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: No? You don't like horror?
PART.2: I used to but my wife no,
so I stopped to do that.
PART.1: But you prefer the horror
of the spirits or the horror of killing?
SUPERVISOR: Gore.
PART.2: The killing and the actions
I can watch any movie
but my wife no.
PART.2: When she looks
that movies killing people
she cannot look.
PART.2: Even if she know
this is a movie she cannot.
PART.1: She can't, ok.