PART.1: Ok.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: Ten questions.
PART.1: Ok, we can start.
PART.2: Is it a carnivore?
PART.1: A what?
PART.2: Carnivore, that eats only the animals.
PART.2: That eats only flesh
or is it like a...
PART.1: I don't know,
I don't think it eats flesh,
does it?
PART.1: I am not sure,
you can ask me another question.
PART.1: Something easier.
PART.2: Can it fly?
PART.1: Yes!
PART.2: Ok, that makes sense.
PART.1: It can fly, so, what about mine?
Can it fly?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Ok, that's enough.
PART.2: Does it eat with its paws?
PART.2: You know, some animals
eat like pitting from the ground
and some grab and then eat.
PART.2: Is it like using its paws
while eating or...?
PART.2: No, you have to answer
with yes or no so,
does it use its paws to eat?
PART.2: Like its feet to eat?
PART.1: I think so,
it has strong paws.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.2: You can go next.
PART.1: So mine does not fly.
PART.1: Does it have one color
or does it have different colors?
PART.2: I should answer
in yes or no or...?
PART.1: Really?
PART.2: It has more than one color.
PART.1: Ok, it has more than one color.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Ok, your question.
PART.2: Does it hunt?
PART.1: Does it what?
PART.2: Hunt, like for prey for eating.
PART.1: Probably.
PART.2: Ok, your question.
PART.1: I can have more than one
color and how many or does it...?
PART.1: It is only yes or no questions?
PART.2: I don't know,
we can be...
PART.1: I don't know,
last time we were like just...
PART.2: Ok, so whatever.
PART.1: So, how many legs
does it have?
PART.2: It's like two.
PART.1: Two...
PART.1: Two and it doesn't fly?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: I am not sure about this one,
but I mean little...
PART.1: Maybe legs and hands.
PART.1: Hands, I would say yes,
it can use legs and hands
as well so...
PART.1: Ok.
PART.2: It has legs, it has four legs
and the front legs
are also hands.
PART.2: I don't know,
it's a bit confusing.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.2: So, my question.
PART.2: It can fly, it can hunt,
does it have like a nest
in the trees or in the mountains?
PART.1: In trees.
PART.2: In trees.
PART.2: Ok, your question.
PART.1: Can it climb trees?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: I think I know,
I think I know.
PART.2: What??
PART.1: Ok, don't worry,
your question.
PART.1: Maybe,
maybe I'm guessing wrong.
PART.2: Does it have
like a really good eye sight?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Ok, I think I know it.
PART.1: Maybe you know it.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: It can have
I think maybe a good night vision.
PART.1: Because it is like a night thing.
PART.2: I am not sure, I don't
think so, I wouldn't say it has a
good night vision.
PART.1: No, no, I am talking about yours.
PART.2: Ah, mine? It has a good night vision?
Ok, I know exactly what it is.
PART.2: Its an owl!
PART.1: Yes!! I think mine is a bear?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: No? Oh no! I am wrong!
PART.2: It can climb and has two legs
but with hands...
PART.1: Can I change color?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Ok, because I though
in something that changes colors.
PART.1: Where does it live?
Does it live in the forest?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: All animals live in the forest.
PART.1: What kind of question is that?
PART.1: Can you find it in the zoo?
PART.2: I think yes.
PART.1: Is it small?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Is it a squirrel?
PART.2: Yes!!
PART.1: Yes!! It's cute actually.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: It eats with hands, nice!
PART.1: The owl looks really nice.
PART.2: When you said the night
I already knew it was the owl.
PART.2: I was going for eagle.
PART.1: I thought so when you said
strong eye sight.
PART.1: But no, so...
PART.1: Yes, yes, this could be.
PART.1: This is nice, but
sometimes, in the last one I got a
chameleon?
PART.2: A chameleon then,
a lizard than changes colors.
PART.1: Yes and I don't know
what it is called, so it's a lizard
and my friend was like...
PART.2: A chameleon then,
a lizard than changes colors.
PART.1: Yes and I don't know
what it is called, so it's a lizard
and my friend was like...
PART.1: You are right!
PART.2: Yes, you are right.
PART.1: And she got a rhino, rhino?
PART.2: Rhino, like the dinosaur, yes.
PART.1: She also like described it
like this thing, that thing,
i don't know how it is called!
PART.1: Ok, you are right.
PART.1: Just get over it.
PART.2: I got a pelican
in the previous one.
PART.1: A pelican what is that?
PART.2: It is like a bird
that eats fishes in the sea.
PART.1: A pelican what is that?
PART.2: It is like a bird
that eats fishes in the sea.
PART.1: That's why you were asking
if it eats with its paws.
PART.2: Yes, i was asking that
if it is like a chicken
that just picks things.
PART.1: That's the second bird you get.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: This looks good.
PART.1: It is also a nice game.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: If you know
all the names in English.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: If you know
all the names in English.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: We used to play this game
but like acting.
PART.1: I remember
there is this like heads-up game
but something like this
but with your phone
PART.1: and then the other person
should act it,
PART.1: it's like a sequence
and you have a timer, that's tough.
PART.1: It is nice also,
I remember something like this.
PART.1: But I don't know,
sometimes it was like movies
or like actors or songs.
PART.1: It was also nice.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Good times.
PART.1: It was nice.
PART.1: So, what do you do
now for fun?
PART.2: I mostly play ping-pong,
like table tennis.
PART.2: We play in some parks,
like the Ciutadella park
or in the Barceloneta park.
PART.2: Have you seen Barcelona a lot?
PART.1: We've been here a month,
a month no,
a week, sorry.
PART.2: A week, not enough.
PART.1: Not enough, yes,
but we've been to the beach
PART.1: and I've seen some tables
and it is nice to have
something in common like this.