PART.2: Then, what is your name?
PART.1: I'm Meysam.
PART.2: Meysam.
PART.1: Meysam.
PART.1: With 'M' at the end.
PART.1: I'm from Iran.
PART.1: I'm thirty-six years old.
PART.1: I'm doing research for a
long time here.
PART.1: Maybe it's now eight years.
PART.2: Eight years?
PART.2: So you're
living in Barcelona for 8 years?
PART.1: Yeah. Eight years.
PART.2: Erm...
PART.1: I don't know, you
can ask questions...
PART.1: I don't know what to say.
PART.2: I can tell you my name.
PART.2: My name is Irineo.
PART.2: Well, it's not a common name.
PART.2: I'm from Brazil.
PART.2: So it's not a Brazilian name.
PART.2: But it's easy to...to...
to remember because here they have
like because here they have like the
Pireneo's mountains right?
PART.2: So you just have to take
the 'P' out, the first letter and
then you have my name.
PART.2: Like Irineo.
PART.2: So it's very easy for the
Catalans and for people here.
PART.1: Is there any relationship
with the Pyrenees?
PART.2: I don't ...
PART.2: I don't know.
PART.2: I don't have any idea.
PART.2: I think that the name is like
Rumanian or something like that.
PART.2: I'm not sure.
PART.2: What I know is that.
PART.2: I met one guy which is Irineo in
my life, which is my father.
PART.2: My father is Irineo as well.
PART.1: Really?
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: So, he's Irineo
and I'm Irineo junior.
PART.2: We have this in Brazil when you
have the same name as your father
you put like 'junior'.
PART.1: I see Brazil.
PART.1: I see this is...
PART.1: Portuguese...
PART.2: Might be, might be...
PART.1: The names are
like two lines.
PART.2: Er...yeah.
PART.1: Six or seven different.
PART.2: Especially in Portugal.
PART.2: I have a friend in Portugal that
has a long names, like four last
names and it's a mess.
PART.2: But I have just one last name
but my family is actually from
Italy.
PART.2: Coz like my grand-grand-fathers
they left Italy and they went to
Brazil.
PART.2: This was very normal
like 150 years ago...
PART.2: More or less.
PART.2: When a lot of Italians they
left Europe to go to South America.
PART.1: Because of resources
or...
PART.2: Yeah...because they
have like...
PART.2: They were agricultors and
they have a lot of land there.
PART.2: it was like land with no peoples
...no...so they went there to work
in the land.
PART.2: So the Brazilian government and also
the Argentinian, the Uruguayan.
PART.2: I think that they gave like land
for them to produce so then they
came to Brazil.
PART.2: So that's why we have a lot of
Germans, Italians, Polish like in
the...in South America
PART.2: But especially in Argentina
and Brazil.
PART.2: So my last name is actually
from Italy.
PART.2: It's like Savignano.
PART.1: Um...
PART.2: And I've been here
for two and a half years.
PART.2: I came here to make my Master and
then I'm just like, I'm working out
like this last year at least.
PART.1: So you are working?
PART.2: Yes, I'm working now.
PART.1: You abandoned research?
PART.2: Not research.
PART.2: I'm not from the academic world,
no.
PART.2: I just like work...like normal.
PART.2: I ...My company is at the
Torre Agbar.
PART.2: You know the Torre Agbar?
PART.2: Like the colours and stuff?
PART.2: Yeah. I work there.
PART.2: Inside.
PART.2: So I work for an internet
company. Yeah.
PART.1: Your field is Computer
Science?
PART.2: No, not Computer Science
I studied Business Administration.
PART.2: So I have a friend that is I
think is like part of the study and
that's why I'm here.
PART.2: But I'm not a researcher...no.
PART.2: I don't have have any idea of all
these cameras do...is like...
PART.1: But in business is there
any PhD or that...?
PART.2: Yeah. Yes.
PART.2: There are PhDs in
business. Yeah.
PART.2: Um...I did my Master in Project
Management.
PART.2: So that like basically you learn
how to manage a project... all that
to work with things...
PART.2: But yeah, of course, there are
like PhDs in this area... as... as
jobs...
PART.2: Because then you can mix
like economics with business and
even math.
PART.2: You can do like mathematics with
business and all that.
PART.2: You can apply different fields.
PART.1: I think this field is
one of thegood opportunities.
PART.2: Uh hu...um...
PART.1: to take jobs, I think...
PART.1: Yeah I think it changes a lot.
PART.1: It's very dynamic.
PART.1: It depends on the
economy.
PART.2: Exactly...
PART.2: If the economy is down, you go
down as well.
PART.2: So it's very...it's like....
it's not a stable job.
PART.1: I think it's quite
common for all the jobs with respect
to the economy.
PART.1: If the economy goes
down everybody go down.
PART.2: Yeah...it's true.
PART.1: In Computer Science for
instance nobody is going to invest.
PART.2: That's right.
PART.1: In Artificial
Intelligence then everybody is going
to lose jobs.
PART.1: It's because you need to sell the
product...and if the economy goes
down...
PART.2: Right. Definitely...
PART.1: The company can not
pay you...yeah.