PART.2: Ok!
PART.1: So, you prefer to follow?
PART.2: Let's have just a short view
and we can first, ok.
PART.2: I would follow maybe a bit
and we can search
for the small pieces maybe?
PART.1: Ok, for the pieces, yes.
PART.2: I would follow maybe a bit
and we can search
for the small pieces maybe?
PART.1: Ok, for the pieces, yes.
PART.2: I am not sure
if you were doing LEGO
PART.2: when you were young,
maybe you can...
PART.1: Not, I am not a LEGO...
PART.2: To use the best tactic,
I have only a little process,
PART.2: so I know what they are doing
but I was not doing it.
PART.1: Not, I am not a LEGO...
PART.2: To use the best tactic,
I have only a little process,
PART.2: so I know what they are doing
but I was not doing it.
PART.1: Yes, just...
PART.2: Just searching and is this pink?
PART.1: This one I think, right?
PART.2: Yes, that's good,
what is this?
PART.2: Is it pink or something?
PART.1: Here!
PART.2: Yes, it is here.
PART.2: Like this.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: It is like this and this.
PART.1: Yes, so far so good, right?
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: And then this one...
PART.1: Should be this?
Do you think?
PART.2: Yes, that's good.
PART.1: Should be this?
Do you think?
PART.2: And some long go on.
PART.1: Maybe this one?
PART.2: No, this is a wrong one
and we did it before.
PART.1: No, no.
PART.2: No, this is a wrong one
and we did it before.
PART.1: No, no.
PART.2: This is a challenge
if we don't fight.
PART.2: Here it is!
PART.1: Yes, good!
PART.1: Four, five...
PART.2: Ok, this one?
PART.1: This one perhaps?
PART.2: Yes, that's good.
PART.1: Yes and I think
we need two of these, right?
PART.2: I can do it if you want.
PART.1: It is fine,
we are a teamwork.
PART.2: Yes, right!
PART.2: No...
PART.2: This I put it down.
PART.1: I think this goes...
PART.1: Here and then
we need four of these!
PART.2: But it turned it around
and then they put this, ok.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Nodded, ok.
PART.1: Here?
PART.2: Yes, one, ok.
PART.2: Here, here, ok.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.1: Let's see, two of each.
PART.2: And the black.
PART.1: This one could be this?
PART.2: Yes, this was good.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.1: And here.
PART.2: Here we go.
PART.1: Yes, yes.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: Eight!
PART.1: I think is this one.
PART.2: Yes...
PART.1: This one.
PART.1: Oh, yes!
Actually is here.
PART.2: Cool!
PART.1: Two, let's see...
PART.2: But it is a different one,
it is like a closed one.
PART.2: I am not sure
if there's an open eye.
PART.1: This one is open.
PART.2: I am not sure
if there's an open eye.
PART.1: This one is open.
PART.2: Ah, it's better.
PART.1: Two open and this one?
PART.2: Yes and this one.
PART.1: And this one, right?
PART.2: Ok, yes.
PART.2: It looks good
so I will place it like this.
PART.2: We have it on the side, maybe?
PART.2: Then we can put
the eyes on it.
PART.2: And we have some... Yes.
PART.1: Yes and then...
PART.2: Just move it
and turn it around again.
PART.1: Yes and then...
PART.2: Just move it
and turn it around again.
PART.2: No, that's weird.
PART.1: Yes, it should be here I think.
PART.2: Yes, like this?
PART.1: No, I think
is the other way around, yes!
PART.2: Ah, it's looking down,
I remember, ok.
PART.2: It is like this,
I was like it should be up
but it is ok, maybe.
PART.1: This is eight and nine,
let's see.
PART.1: Two black.
PART.2: Yes, this one
is already collected.
PART.1: Yes, it is like
getting easy for us.
PART.2: But we need this one.
PART.1: Yes, these LEGOs are more...
On my time it was not like this.
PART.2: But you had it as a toy?
PART.1: Well, we used to have LEGOs
as well but not this one,
this one is very like modern I think.
PART.2: Yes, yes.
PART.1: Mines are like...
PART.2: Usually you had playing stuff
and you had to be creative,
like having eyes?
PART.2: I've never seen it before.
PART.1: That's right,
that's when I say
they are like modern.
PART.1: And then we have...
PART.2: Some green ones...
PART.1: Yes, some grass I think.
PART.1: Not this one...
PART.1: Here and here.
PART.1: Right, but I think
there is like foot...
PART.2: And we put it like this,
like it is eating...
PART.1: Right, but I think
there is like foot...
PART.2: And we put it like this,
like it is eating...
PART.1: It is like, yes...
PART.2: Is it like fitting like this?
PART.1: But I think...
PART.2: It looks good I think.
PART.2: It looks similar.
PART.1: Yes, it looks similar
but this seems
that there isn't more space here?
PART.2: Is it higher here?
Because this one don't look like,
it can't fit on it at all...
PART.1: Yes, it looks similar
but this seems
that there isn't more space here?
PART.2: Is it higher here?
Because this one don't look like,
it can't fit on it at all...
PART.1: Yes, what...
PART.1: Maybe there is something here.
PART.1: See? There's no space here?
PART.2: Oh, there's no space...
PART.2: We should have placed it there.
PART.1: Yes, here is...
PART.2: This must be same heigh as...
PART.2: These are brown...
PART.2: Like this.
PART.2: And this must be one for it.
PART.1: Yes, definitely yes.
PART.2: That looks good.
PART.2: It makes me more sense,
before it was ourselves
putting them on the floor.
PART.1: Yes, now is more like that.
PART.2: Like this though,
that looks good
because it is placed like this.
PART.2: Beautiful!
PART.1: Yes, but do we have
to take pieces
or just the same pieces
PART.1: but they were like
in a brown position?
PART.2: I don't get it, sorry.
PART.1: I was saying like it was wrong
because we misplaced the pieces.
PART.2: Yes, I really think...
Let's have a look.
PART.2: That was this weird moment.
PART.2: This weird moment
where we were asked if we...
PART.2: No, it is a shoulder,
it should be connected
this one to this one.
PART.2: I haven't seen it then.
PART.1: Ok, ok.
PART.2: Then afterwards
we could have seen it
PART.2: because then I just ignored it
because it is brown
and not all...
PART.2: But it is ok.
PART.1: Ah, not the same color.
PART.2: Then afterwards
we could have seen it
PART.2: because then I just ignored it
because it is brown
and not all...
PART.2: But it is ok.
PART.1: Ah, not the same color.
PART.2: Oh, we found a mistake
and now it's done.
PART.1: Oh, we just learn
from the "mistakes".
PART.2: Next time I play LEGO
I will be much better, sure.
PART.1: But in my time it was different,
like faces like this? No way...
PART.2: No, this is very special.
PART.2: You can reuse it,
I mean, it is only possible
to build it like this
PART.2: but you can use it
for maybe a sword or...
PART.1: Yes, yes.
PART.2: But I think we don't need
to be more creative anymore,
just follow this.
PART.1: Yes, that's it,
because I was like remembering
PART.1: and I don't know
if they still have to follow the order,
so sometimes you just have
like pieces to invent.
PART.2: To put them together.
PART.1: Yes, that's it,
because I was like remembering
PART.1: and I don't know
if they still have to follow the order,
so sometimes you just have
like pieces to invent.
PART.2: To put them together.
PART.1: Yes, just like to be creative.
PART.2: After some time,
you need to be creative I think
PART.2: because you just mix
every package together
PART.2: and you are just
like you don't find
anything anymore so you have a look
a pick another color
PART.1: To make something different, yes.
PART.1: Yes, LEGO is like everywhere.
PART.2: But there is amazing things
with electric LEGOs
and big ones,
PART.2: I have a little brother
who was working for two weeks
PART.2: and sitting there putting things together
until it was like this big machine.
PART.1: Yes, you can view like cities
with all the lights
and of course they have
the Star Wars LEGO.
PART.2: Oh, sure...
PART.2: But usually
you don't play with it,
I have never seen someone...
PART.2: You just build it and then is like
dust on the shelf.
PART.1: Yes, for the creation,
just for the creation.
PART.2: But usually
you don't play with it,
I have never seen someone...
PART.2: You just build it and then is like
dust on the shelf.
PART.1: Yes, for the creation,
just for the creation.
PART.2: So, look at this!
SUPERVISOR: All right, perfect!