PART.1: So 152?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: I am 43.
PART.2: Oh, so you started
at the morning already?
PART.1: No, I am just...
I don't know, a random number.
PART.1: My name is Irine.
PART.2: Irine?
PART.1: Irine, yes, that's right.
PART.2: Ah, ok.
PART.1: I am from Brazil.
PART.2: Ah, ok, ok.
PART.2: And your name?
PART.2: Viola.
PART.1: Viola?
PART.1: Viola.
PART.2: Yes, that sounds good.
PART.1: Viola, ok, where are you from?
PART.2: Germany.
PART.1: Germany, ok.
PART.1: Do you live here in Barcelona?
PART.2: No, I just visit a friend here
and she is organizing it
so she was like:
PART.2: "Do you want to see
where I am working?"
PART.1: Do you live here in Barcelona?
PART.2: No, I just visit a friend here
and she is organizing it
so she was like:
PART.2: "Do you want to see
where I am working?"
PART.2: I was like:
"Yes, why not?
It could be quite interesting".
PART.1: "Oh, maybe I prefer
to go to the beach".
PART.2: I am already a week here
so it is fine.
PART.1: Ah, ok, very good.
PART.2: I am already a week here
so it is fine.
PART.1: Ah, ok, very good.
PART.2: She was working
with us in Germany
so it is very interesting for me
PART.2: She was working
with us in Germany
so it is very interesting for me
PART.2: to see the research right now,
so I was really interested.
PART.2: I asked her: "Can I go there?"
PART.1: Ah, ok.
PART.2: So it was ok.
PART.1: Ah, that's good.
PART.1: And how many days
are you going to stay here?
PART.2: Only one week,
tomorrow we are leaving
very early so it was already a week.
PART.1: Ah, ok.
PART.1: I live in Barcelona
for almost three years now.
PART.2: Oh, wow!
How did it come to come you here?
PART.1: I started as a master,
I came here to study.
PART.2: Ok. studying.
PART.1: I started as a master,
I came here to study.
PART.1: Then I have a master
in Project Management
and then I decided to stay.
PART.1: I was doing
my Italian citizenship
in the meantime of my master.
PART.2: What is it?
PART.1: Italian citizenship,
my family is from Italy,
I am Brazilian
PART.1: but my family came
a long time ago
PART.1: so we can apply
for the double citizenship.
PART.2: So you need to do a test
or are you just...?
PART.2: Because you have some relatives
and it's fine and you just have it?
PART.1: Yes, for the Italians yes,
the problem is that
there is a lot of bureaucracy,
PART.1: you have to find all the birth
certificates from very, very far
from my family.
PART.1: So, I mean,
you don't have to speak Italian
but you have to find the papers...
PART.1: And I was able to have
the Italian passport
and then I decided to stay here.
PART.1: Well, at least for the moment
and then I was able
to find a job and so on.
PART.1: Where do you live in Germany?
PART.2: Near Frankfurt,
do you know Darmstadt?
PART.1: Frankfurt yes.
PART.2: But Darmstadt no one knows,
it is a university city
so there are a lot of students.
PART.1: But it is very close from Frankfurt.
PART.2: Yes, half an hour.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.2: But it is like a big city.
PART.1: Right, but your family
is from the same place
or you live...?
PART.2: Yes, the same,
it is like again half an hour from it
and where actually I grow up.
PART.1: Ah, ok.
PART.2: So, I actually stayed
around the area in Frankfurt
but, yes, I am happy.
PART.1: Ah, ok, good.
PART.1: Is it your first time in Barcelona?
PART.2: Yes, I never visited it before.
PART.2: I mean, it is very touristic
but it is nice to have
someone here,
PART.2: this is very cool and someone can
tell you things like: "This is cool
or this is cool".
PART.2: And you are not
the typical tourist walking around
like "I don't know what to do".
PART.1: Yes, definitely.
PART.1: There is a lot of things to do,
I agree with you
that there are a lot of tourists,
specially in this time of the year.
PART.2: Oh, yes.
PART.1: There is like the summer
that is calmly, the city is warmer
like we have more visitors.
PART.1: But it is nice, I like it.
PART.1: I came to study,
but like open-minded
to say maybe it is a place to visit,
PART.1: to live and of course
it is one city when you visit it
as a tourist
PART.1: and it is a different city
when you actually live,
PART.1: But I am having a good time,
I don't have complains
and I have friends already.
PART.2: That's a point, I mean,
you studied here
PART.2: and you have a lot of people,
you met a lot of people.
PART.1: Yes, now I am working so yes.
PART.2: But you want to stay here?
PART.1: Well, that's a good question.
PART.2: Ok, no one can tell.
PART.1: It's hard to say,
for the moment yes
but of course I miss my family,
PART.1: so sometimes I say maybe
but for the moment yes.
PART.1: Let's say, two or three weeks ago
my parents came for the first time.
PART.2: Yes, wow!
PART.1: So it was nice for the
first time.
PART.2: Yes, wow!
PART.1: So it was nice for the
first time.
PART.2: For the first time,
it is far away
so it is quite an effort for them.
PART.1: It is far
and they have a certain age
so the trip is not easy for them.
PART.1: But they had a very good time.
PART.2: That's nice, it's cool.
PART.1: So, first in Europe
and from here we went to Italy.
PART.2: Ah, ok.
PART.1: So, we stayed in Milano,
in Verona, in Venecia as well.
PART.2: Ah, it's really nice Venecia.
PART.1: It is Venice, right?
PART.1: So, it was nice.
PART.2: Ah, it's really nice Venecia.