PART.1: This one...
PART.2: Ready...
PART.2: Go...
PART.2: OK.
PART.2: We have to find this piece...
PART.1: This one or...
PART.1: This one...
PART.2: This one right.
PART.2: Then the brown ones.
PART.2: It's like one, two, three, four
and maybe this one.
PART.1: It's a three.
PART.2: Oh. A four.
PART.2: This one and the same
but two...probably this one...
PART.1: The grey one...
PART.2: Grey or black?
PART.1: It's kind of grey...
PART.1: I don't know...
PART.1: Do we have any grey ones?
PART.1: Grey....not this one....
PART.2: What do you think?
PART.2: Let's try out that one?
PART.1: I do not see a lot
of grey ones...
PART.2: This one?
PART.1: No. It's not the one.
PART.1: Maybe it's...yeah... this one?
PART.2: Yeah, let's try that
one then.
PART.2: So let's put this one here.
PART.2: You want right over...yeah.
PART.2: And this one in the middle.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: Great.
PART.2: One block.
PART.2: Green and red.
PART.2: And one like maroon
the other one.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: That one here, OK?
PART.2: And...here...
PART.2: Er...Woah!
PART.2: OK, yeah good.
PART.2: OK. Here is black...and here.
PART.2: Well.
PART.2: Is black.
PART.2: OK.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: So far so good.
PART.2: Five.
PART.2: OK.
PART.2: This one.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: We need...two.
PART.2: Here...
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: And this should be the
centre for like two tyres.
PART.2: So. Here.
PART.2: Right.
PART.1: The other one.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: Now one of these and two of
these ones...should be this.
PART.2: Can it be this one?
PART.2: And one more...like this one...
PART.1: This one.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: Very good.
PART.2: OK. So then...
PART.2: You wanna pick this one?
PART.2: Ah. On the back.
PART.2: I think in the last one.
PART.1: The last one.
PART.2: Yeah. Coz there is like one
green...
PART.2: This one.
PART.2: Yeah...here.
PART.2: And here...yes...
PART.2: Seven...
PART.2: Don't find any one...so this
one here...right?
PART.2: And this one should be...
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: In front.
PART.2: And in back.
PART.2: Now wheels...forbidden for
these ones.
PART.2: It should be this...I think.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: Yeah, I don't know for sure.
PART.2: Gonna get my last...
this one...this one...out
PART.2: And...yeah...
PART.2: Ok.
PART.2: How do we... ah... we have to put
inside.
PART.2: Yeah it should work...
PART.2: Inside...
PART.2: But I don't know if...
PART.2: Ah OK...
PART.2: Coz this one is go outside, and
this one is inside so then we
should.
PART.2: It is...yeah it works...
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: And then we move with nine.
PART.2: Six.
PART.2: Yep.
PART.2: We're done.
PART.2: It really works.
PART.2: Nice.
PART.2: I'm not.
PART.2: Erm.
PART.2: When I was a kid I
don'tusually like play with legos.
PART.2: It's not... it's more like modern
for the new generations, I'd say.
PART.1: I used to play with
legos but not this...advanced.
PART.1: Just this kind of legos.
PART.2: Because you don't have
like build these things....
PART.2: just like blocks...
PART.2: Right.
PART.2: Blocks.
PART.2: Not this one.
PART.2: No.
PART.1: It should be a sheep
I think.
PART.1: This one.
PART.2: So you have like eyes
we don't have...like these pieces
impossible...just...just
regular blocks.
PART.2: This one is actually nice...
PART.1: The designing is kind of.
PART.1: I don't know if it's
game or some toys.
PART.2: Yeah, I believe that like on
these box which is like have like a
mix of lot of things you can build;
PART.2: several things like small,
these ones...you can do.
PART.2: You just have to have
the instructions...
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.1: OK.
PART.1: Maybe.
PART.2: OK!
PART.2: Ah. Take out.
PART.2: We already know
that we have to do it and undo it.