PART.2: So, let’s try...
PART.1: Now, we go
PART.2: Let’s try to keep it in the English language, for sure.
PART.1: Let’s try to keep in English, exactly.
PART.2: so,
PART.1: how did you like the last the last episode?
PART.2: Of Game of Thrones?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: I mean, I was so excited when it came out, and when I saw it was so long, I was even more excited...
PART.1: I don’t, I don’t remember [MASKED]
PART.2: [MASKED], remember?
PART.1: Ah, yes.
PART.2: The battle that they’ve been building up for... 8 years, and that I thought it was going to be the end, end...
PART.1: you think each season took the whole year? I’m not quite sure.
PART.2: It came out on the first, like the first episode came out in 2008
PART.1: Seriously?
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.1: Oh, [MASKED]
PART.2: [MASKED] fucking years.
PART.2: And I always thought that the, like the whole, like since the first episode has always been like the winters are coming...
PART.1: Right, and now...
PART.2: I thought they were building the end of the end, but no, the end is gonna be Cersei being a bitch, and the end, like...
PART.2: Remember?
PART.1: Yeah, but there could be a second king, or... Oh! There could be a queen, actually.
PART.1: We didn't think [MASKED]
PART.1: [MASKED] going on".
PART.2: The queen of ice... Because, I... You know, Jon Snow?
PART.2: He made like a... like a... interview, like a talk show or... And they were asking: "What's the end like?", "What's the end...", they kept asking him before it came out, and he's like: "Yeah, it's something you're never gonna expect".
PART.2: Like, it's something that I didn't even expect, when I read it, i was like, what the fuck?
PART.2: And he told his wife, you know, his wife is like... "You know nothing Jon Snow".
PART.1: Oh, true, that's true.
PART.2: She's out of the show, so she didn't know what the fuck was going on in the screenplay, and everything.
PART.2: And he told her at the end, and she was so pi [MASKED]
PART.2: [MASKED] would you tell me that?"
PART.1: It could actually happen, it could actually be like that.
PART.2: There could be a queen.
PART.1: It would make a lot of sense.
PART.2: Or maybe Cersei becomes the Ice Queen.
PART.2: Maybe that's how everything starts, where did the Ice King come from? I mean, maybe he was a king before.
PART.1: How did the ice army even start?
PART.1: That's what I don't understand, I understand that there's one, that they always got more and more, because they have this weird power going on, but...
PART.2: I don't know.
PART.2: And they say always that... [MASKED]
PART.2: [MASKED] nights, so, like, this war has happened a lot of times before.
PART.2: And this time they have killed them, but that doesn't mean that they're gone forever, that means they're gonna come back again, there's gonna be another long night, you know?
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.2: So, who knows.
PART.1: Put Cersei on the top.
PART.2: Either Cersei fucks everyone up and she becomes a queen...
PART.2: Or the Ice People come back...
PART.1: But don't forget that it's still about that Jon is actually the real heir to the throne.
PART.2: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
PART.1: So, that's gonna happen too, somehow.
PART.2: ... was like "Ah!"
PART.2: instead of... remember when he told her: "I'm actually your brother's son"?
PART.2: She was like "Ah!", instead of "Oh my God, your my family", she was like "Ah! You wanna take my throne away from me? Bitch!"
PART.1: Yeah, yeah, of course.
PART.1: It had to be actually very, very strange for them to film that scene, right? The loving scene.
PART.2: That's a weird love.
PART.2: I think so.
PART.2: I mean, they're both married, I think.
PART.2: I mean, Jon Snow is married.
PART.1: Yeah, no, because they got friends and everything, thoughout the years, and then they had to make this love scene, it was probably super strange.
PART.2: I mean, Arya, man.
PART.2: She started the show when she was literally 12 and she, like, had this sex scene at the end...
PART.1: Yeah, she was so cute in the beginning, she was such a sweetheart. Sansa too.
PART.2: Like, at the beginning, beginning, before everything went out in Winterfell, remember when she was like training with this guy and the dancer... That was so [MASKED]
PART.1: Yeah, yeah.
PART.1: King Geoffrey!
PART.2: Motherfucker.
PART.1: I cut my finger before, when we did the... No, actually I cut my finger at 100 montaditos when I opened the menu before...
PART.2: Shit, papercuts are the worst.
PART.1: No, it's a plastic cut, what is even worse.
PART.2: Oops.
PART.1: How long do we have to do this?
PART.2: I have no clue.
PART.2: But let's talk about the triple planning.
PART.1: The... Which one?
PART.2: The... [MASKED]
PART.2: [MASKED] we had, the Whatsapp group.
PART.1: Yeah. No one was really answering, like I know that I have the drivers license, like a lot, that has one, no one else has his drivers license, which means... people, but...
PART.2: Yeah!
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: But do you wanna go so many people, though?
PART.2: We're not ten. Or...?
PART.1: I don't know.
PART.2: I keep switching.
PART.1: I know, it's really hard to only speak in English, it's getting me very like..."nieh".
PART.1: No, I think it's you, it's me, it's Carlota, Victoria, Elio... And maybe we could either do like a smaller group with like one car, maybe?
PART.2: Carlota, Victoria, Elio, Alex... Julia?
PART.2: I would rather do that actually, if not, it's gonna be way too like...
PART.1: It could be fun, though, it could be really fun if like 10-15 people would come.
PART.2: Yeah but... Julia, for ex... Like, you have a good relationwhip with her, no offense, or something, but like, I don't know if I wanna be on a car, on a trip for three days with Julia, and if Julia comes, Isa is gonna come too.
PART.2: I can't sit, eat in each other's face anymore, like I literally can't. Like, okay, you love each other, fine, but, like, can you love each other behind the closed doors?