PART.1: This one...
PART.2: Ready...Go...
PART.2: OK. We have to find
this piece...
PART.1: This one or...
PART.1: This one...
PART.2: This one right.
Then the brown ones.
PART.2: It's like one, two, three, four
and maybe this one.
PART.1: It's a three.
PART.2: Oh. A four.
PART.2: This one and the same
but two...probably this one...
PART.1: The grey one...
PART.2: Grey or black?
PART.1: It's kind of grey...
I don't know...
PART.1: Do we have any grey ones?
PART.1: Grey....not this one....
PART.2: hat do you think?
Let's try out that one?
PART.1: I do not see a lot
of grey ones...
PART.2: This one?
PART.1: No. It's not the one.
Maybe it's...yeah... this one?
PART.2: Yeah, let's try
that one then.
PART.2: So let's put this one here.
PART.2: You want right over...yeah
PART.2: And this one in the middle. Yeah.
PART.2: Great.
PART.2: One block. Green and red.
PART.2: And one like maroon the other one.
PART.2: Yeah. That one here, OK?
PART.2: And...here...
PART.2: Er...Woah! OK, yeah good.
PART.2: OK. Here is black...and here. Well.
Is black. OK.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: OK. So far so good.
PART.2: Five.
PART.2: OK. This one.
PART.2: Yeah. We need...two
PART.2: Here...
PART.2: Yeah. And this should be the centre
for like two tyres.
PART.2: So. Here.
PART.2: Right.
PART.2: The other one.
PART.2: Yeah. Now one of these and two of
these ones...should be this.
PART.2: Can it be this one?
PART.2: And one more...like this one...
PART.1: This one.
PART.2: Yeah.  Very good.
OK. So then...
PART.2: You wanna pick this one?
PART.2: Ah. On the back.
PART.2: I think in the last one.
PART.1: The last one.
PART.1: Yeah. Coz there is like one green...
PART.1: This one.
PART.1: Yeah...here.
PART.1: And here...yes...
PART.1: Seven...
PART.1: Don't find any one...so this
one here...right?
PART.1: And this one should be...
PART.1: Yeah
PART.1: In front. And in back.
PART.1: Now wheels...forbidden for
these ones.
PART.1: It should be this...I think.
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.1: Yeah, I don't know for sure.
PART.1: Yeah. Gonna get my last...
this one...this one...out
PART.1: And...yeah...Ok
PART.1: How do we ...ah...we have to put
inside
PART.1: Yeah it should work...
PART.1: Inside...
PART.1: But I don't know if...Ah OK...
PART.1: Coz this one is go outside, and
this one is inside so then we should
PART.1: It is...yeah it works...
PART.1: Yeah. And then we move with nine.
Six.
PART.1: Yep. We're done. It really works.
PART.1: It really works.  Nice.
PART.1: I'm not. Erm.  When I was a kid I
don'tusually like play with legos.
PART.1: It's not...it's more like modern
PART.1: for the new generations, I'd say.
PART.1: I used to play with
legos but not this...advanced.
PART.1: Just this kind of legos
PART.2: Because you don't have
like build these things....
PART.2: just like blocks...
PART.2: Right
PART.2: Blocks. Not this one. No.
PART.1: It should be a sheep
I think. This one.
PART.2: So you have like eyes
we don't have...like these pieces
PART.2: impossible...just...just
regular blocks
PART.2: This one is actually nice...
PART.1: he designing is kind of
I don't know if it's game or some toys
PART.1: Yeah, I believe that like on these
box which is like have like a mix of lot
PART.1: of things you can build; several things
like small, these ones...you can do
PART.1: You just have to have
the instructions...
PART.1: Yeah. OK. Maybe.
PART.2: Ah. Take out. We already know
that we have to
PART.2: do it and undo it.