PART.1: Okay
PART.1: He's going out so if you would like we can talk like whatever, asuposed to someone who's sitting here.
PART.2: Yes. Isn't it more...Isn't it more awkward when you're with someone you don't know?
PART.1: Yeah. Games were not awkward because we have a task to do.
PART.2: Before, weren't you supposed to do this warm up first?
PART.1: Yeah sure ...
PART.1: It's fine because you can ask his name. You don't even know his name. Stuff like this.
PART.2: OK, what's your name?
PART.1: Viola and it's really hard because no one knows Viola.
PART.1: But it's in German. I want to be called Viola.
PART.2: I doubt anyone would know my name.
PART.1: Yeza. Yeza. What?
PART.1: Yeza is like...What resemblance is this. ... It's very beautiful.
PART.2: I hope so, I hope so. It would be easier to spell and people will find it. Anywhere.
PART.1: Maybe I should say Viola because people know it but I don't want to be called Viola.
PART.2: Yeah, Viola's OK.
PART.1: Viola.
PART.2: But for this experiment that person is only going to see you maybe. No for like another 40 minutes and forget about you.
PART.1: That's true. I can't remember his name.
PART.2: But it's recorded. Maybe you shouldn't be manipulating your name.
PART.1: Manipulating my name, what?
PART.2: You shouldn't be changing your name because that thing is recorded.
PART.2: Yeah, they can sense you. When you're lying.
PART.1: Oh yeah. Maybe. It would be interesting to see. When your heart rate is going up. Like no pressure.
PART.2: My heart rate is going up. Right now I am nervous. I don't know why.
PART.1: In the beginning I was very nervous but the second time it's okay.
PART.2: And it's with you imagine if it was with someone else.
PART.1: If it was someone else it would be very awkward in the beginning, but after some time you warm up.
PART.1: You're like, OK, your one team together against this task.
PART.2: Oh, okay. That would be nice. So you stop playing against each other.
PART.1: It's really quite good.
PART.1: ... No, I'm sure they'll tell. Sorry.
PART.2: Anyway, don't tell me. So what's for dinner tonight?
PART.1: Something warm ... Soup?
PART.2: The honey was not healthy?
PART.1: I don't know.
PART.1: No. It's getting... Sometimes. I think in the evenings it's always works worse, in the mornings it's fine. I don't know.
PART.2: I hope so.
PART.1: Or we could watch...Should we go to this Catalan restaurant?
PART.2: Oh, maybe we can.
PART.1: I mean we are ...
PART.1: But it's only one hour we have.
PART.1: And we have to go back already.
PART.2: Oh yeah yeah yeah. No no I don’t Alexa can leave with us anyway.
PART.1: But only for us it's only one hour food...for food.
PART.2: I don't think it's an hour because we. Very close to our place, we need like half an hour.
PART.1: All right it was not near of this place.
PART.2: No.
PART.1: No. OK.
PART.2: I was near this tower that looks like a bullet for me, I don't know why.
PART.1: Yeah it's this weird thing like you said.
PART.2: Like you were saying, I don't think it's worth it to go back.
PART.1: Alexa mentioned some burger shop but I don't I'm not sure if I want to eat a burger.
PART.2: I don't like burger.
PART.1: OK then we don't eat there.
PART.2: We can walk around here maybe I don't know.
PART.1: It is up to you.. Some pret.
PART.1: ... I love Pret.
PART.2: Oh we didn't have your green tea.
PART.1: I haven't finished it but I can ...
PART.1: Exactly but I am waiting for you.
PART.2: Waiting for me for what?
PART.2: Oh, a second one. OK yeah.
PART.2: Or we can just go home.
PART.2: Leave me.
PART.1: I'm not sure if it's not nice.
PART.2: What are you going to do at home?
PART.1: Sleeping on this couch. I will sleep on the couch. For 30 minutes. Just imagine this couch.
PART.1: We can't go separated because we have one ticket.
PART.2: I'll see.
PART.1: I complete you.
PART.2: I should take the ticket.
PART.1: I can go shopping.
PART.1: Yeah, yeah ...
PART.1: I think because I have no money left anymore.
PART.2: I don't have a lot of money left either. But I don't have a phone even.
PART.1: That's really scary. So you're really dependent on me.
PART.2: I hate to admit it.
PART.1: Is it scary for you?
PART.2: But I should find a way to recharge online. I tried this morning but it wasn't very obvious. So I said try again.
PART.1: Because for me it's like I can login with mine and I can charge it with my account number from my bank.
PART.2: Oh, okay, okay.
PART.1: It was not possible for you?
PART.2: It was like automatic re-charged whenever my account is less than some thing automatically it recharges. I don't want it to automatically recharge every time. I just like this time.
PART.1: It's not helping because you don't have less. Anything.
PART.1: It's more of a problem because you have ... over.
PART.2: Exactly.
PART.2: I don't know I only saw those two options for automatic re-charging but I didn't see an option for... I just want to recharge it now once.
PART.1: It's so not nice to just cut you off without a warning because there was no SMS or some thing. No message telling you.
PART.2: I think they sent me a warning.
PART.2: ...But not now...
PART.2: I don't know, like your something ends in two weeks.
PART.1: But you're really sure that it's this one. Because...
PART.2: Yeah. It happened before.
PART.1: OK.
PART.2: It happened, I always forget recharging and then charge it.
PART.1: It's already too late.
PART.1: ... I couldn't do this before the internet. I mean, I'm really dependent on this.
PART.1: I mean you're in a new city and you...
PART.2: Oh yeah for a new city it's...
PART.1: OK, last month I was...yeah but OK sure.
PART.1: ...I wouldn't need it.
PART.1: Well it's better to save money.
PART.1: It might be a way to go.