PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: So you just turn around on that pile, yeah, right.
PART.2: What?
PART.2: That's the ghost!
PART.1: That was the ghost.
PART.2: Okay, that's for you.
PART.1: Okay.
PART.2: It's your turn.
PART.2: Eh...
PART.1: It's a... bottle.
PART.2: Why am I so dumb?
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: It's... You're looking at the things, you're like: "Mmm, what is this?
PART.2: I think I'm not really... Like, my brain, like, I get it, but my brain is not processing.
PART.2: Whoo!
PART.1: Oh, I'm not quite sure.
PART.1: Ah! True, matching.
PART.2: Gang, gang!
PART.1: Oh, it's so fucking cute.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.2: Oh, it's my turn.
PART.1: No, shit! No, fuck! Oh, shit! No...
PART.2: Is this, right?
PART.1: Yes. It is.
PART.2: Yeah, you can swear. This is human behaviour, humans swear all the time.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: That's a nice picture.
PART.2: I like that, it looks like me.
PART.2: Eh...
PART.2: Okay. That was for you.
PART.1: Very slowly, but surely.
PART.2: But surely.
PART.2: Oh.
PART.1: Yeah. And I'm still looking like: "Mmm, yeah".
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.2: Cool.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: I won!
PART.1: Javi!
PART.2: Javi!