PART.1: Okay.
PART.1: So do you want to do it like each question.
PART.2: I think so.
PART.1: OK yeah. So should you start or I start?
PART.2: You start. I don't know what kind of questions to ask.
PART.1: OK. Do I live on the land? It's like in the land, in the water or air? I'm asking you do I live on land?
PART.2: It lives on land but it can also go onto other stuff.
PART.1: That's interesting. Thank you.
PART.2: I think it lives on land.
PART.1: I heard other stuff and was like shoot, I don't know.
PART.1: Okay.
PART.2: Can I ask you like how many or is it supposed to be like...
PART.1: How many?
PART.2: How many legs for example.
PART.1: Oh yeah sure.
PART.2: OK, how many legs?
PART.1: Four legs.
PART.2: OK ...
PART.1: And maybe I can extend it a bit more and... I'm not sure.
PART.1: Let me say four legs and something to hold on.
PART.1: And some tail. Or something like this.
PART.2: OK your turn.
PART.2: Okay, that counts.
PART.1: Okay.
PART.1: I can go in the water.
PART.1: Do I have wings?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Oh ok.
PART.2: You don't have wings.
PART.1: Okay.
PART.2: Do I eat bananas?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: No?
PART.1: I think so. I'm not sure. I'm sure you don't eat a banana.
PART.1: I think I know what it eats maybe.
PART.1: I have no wings.
PART.1: No wings. So I can also live on the water so I can go in the water and swim a bit? So I have something to swim?
PART.2: You don’t swim but you can go into water.
PART.1: Okay.
PART.2: Technically you can.
PART.1: Technical. I'm not going down and trying to get...
PART.1: Okay.
PART.2: Four and a tail and doesn't eat bananas.
PART.2: I can't come up with new questions.
PART.1: It's okay...
PART.2: I'm coming up with a very stupid questions.
PART.2: Do I...
PART.2: Can I swim?
PART.1: No, I don't think so.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: Do I have one color or different colors, mixed?
PART.2: One color. That's a good question can I repeat it all the questions?
PART.1: Yeah, it's a good question for you too.
PART.2: OK. Do I have different colors?
PART.1: You can change your colors.
PART.2: Oh.
PART.1: That's very obvious. That's very obvious.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.2: Your turn.
PART.1: OK, my turn. Do I live near the sea? What? No? I thought I lived near the sea. No. OK.
PART.2: No.
PART.1: I thought I know what I am. I don't know where anymore.
PART.2: No, you don't live... You're not a sea animal.
PART.1: I'm more at a lake.
PART.2: But yeah. You can go to a lake to have a wash or something but you're really big for a swim. Like you're really big.
PART.2: A big animal.
PART.1: But I'm swimming. I can swim.
PART.2: No, you can't swim you just go for a wash. Like you can go into the water and and then come out.
PART.1: What? The fuck is this animal?
PART.2: I don't know maybe I'm mssing up for.
PART.1: No it's OK.
PART.2: I don't know what kind of documentary I was watching.
PART.1: It's good.
PART.2: I don't know what documentary I was watching.
PART.1: No it's OK. ... I know I have no idea. You can go.
PART.2: I can change my color so am I a lizard?
PART.1: Oh shit I mixed something up. It's my fault. Is it?
PART.2: Oh OK. You can change your color.
PART.1: I thought. Is this animal changing?
PART.2: I don't know, there is an animal like a lizard that changes their their colors?
PART.1: No, no.
PART.2: Do you have a tail that you can grab into?
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: So do you use it to grab. For grabbing things?
PART.1: Yeah. I'm not... There is another one but maybe it's not changing the color. Sorry I'm looking at the picture and trying to figure out if it's changing the color right now.
PART.1: ...Right now? Is there a movie up on my head?
PART.1: Maybe you don't know the name because you've got everything.
PART.2: Maybe I don't know the name?
PART.1: Let's guess a bit better. I think it changes its color.
PART.2: I'm not counting the questions, are you?
PART.1: OK we had to before. I had forgot. That's not true.
PART.1: We had land, we had... What was I asking afterwards?
PART.2: I said land and then you ask me if I can swim? And then if it's all the same color and then if it's lives near the sea.
PART.1: We have four, okay.
PART.2: It is four questions?
PART.1: Because also you only ask four things. I think it's only four maybe.
PART.1: Because you asked how many foot, how may feet...
PART.2: How many feet. And I also asked different colours.
PART.1: Banana, different colours...
PART.2: And if I'm a lizard.
PART.1: And a lizard, yeah, four. Okay, okay.
PART.2: So four questions.
PART.2: My question again...
PART.1: It's my turn?
PART.2: Your turn?
PART.1: Or are you going to ask some thing else then lizard maybe. I’m not sure.
PART.2: No, your turn, I asked.
PART.1: It’s not written lizard, it's something else written. I'm sure it's one...
PART.2: Is it close to it?
PART.1: Yeah pretty close, I'm not sure what.
PART.2: I don't know...
PART.1: Lizard doesn't change its color I think.
PART.2: There are types. I don't know the name like... it looks like a lizard...
PART.1: Yeah OK I think yeah.
PART.2: ...but has a mouth that captures the insects or something.
PART.1: You have it. You just don't know the name maybe.
PART.2: It's big eyes. Or not..
PART.1: It's a big eye but it's like covered with a skin.
PART.2: It has a skin that does this.
PART.1: Yeah, I think you know it. I think...
PART.2: I don't know what the name is.
PART.1: The name.
PART.2: But you can ask questions and we can put it down...
PART.1: Before I didn't know the name in English...
PART.2: Oh okay.
PART.1: ...so i was just describing it. OK. So I'm at the lake and I'm washing myself there.
PART.2: You're a big.
PART.1: You're big, really big. And one color. You're washing...
PART.2: It's hard.
PART.1: Do I live in a forest?
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.1: Okay, that was already five. I'm living in the forest. And I'm living by the forest.. OK next question, do I live in the zoo? Can I be seen in the zoo or are people taking me as an animal at home or something like this?
PART.2: No, not at home that I know.
PART.1: No?
PART.2: It's big.
PART.1: Big...
PART.2: It's not like this. It's not like elephant big.
PART.1: I just wish...
PART.2: It has something that a unicorn has. I'm giving you so much stuff.
PART.1: It has some thing that a unicorn has.
PART.2: Not exactly that would like some thing like that.
PART.1: It's from Africa?
PART.1: Ah, it's a nasshorn.
PART.2: Maybe it doesn't live in the forest.
PART.1: Come on.
PART.1: It's like it's this one thing coming out of their head.
PART.2: Yes!
PART.1: It's gray. And it's very big.
PART.1: I'm not sure what's in English. It's a nasshorn.
PART.2: It's a rhino.
PART.1: Rhino. OK, well that's chameleon.
PART.2: Chameleon.
PART.1: Yeah, you had it.
PART.2: Oh yeah.
PART.1: We were making things up.
PART.2: But this I don't know, I don't know what that name is... Maybe I should have... It's in... Some movies.
PART.1: I don't know any movies ... what movies?
PART.2: It's like in some animation movies.
PART.1: I know Ratatouille.
PART.2: It's in ice.
PART.2: Ice Age.
PART.2: It's in Ice Age, no?
PART.1: Ice Age it's just this crazy squirrel?
PART.2: Not Ice Age, not Ice Age.
PART.1: Somewhere.
PART.2: In Madagascar. Do you know Madagascar?
PART.1: I know Madagascar, yeah.
PART.2: I think there was one like this or maybe...
PART.1: I've seen them all. But I forgot them all but I can't remember that this animal... Yours, is there...
PART.2: Chameleon, okay.
PART.1: I've seen it once in a zoo. It's really impressive how big they are.
PART.2: Rhino and chameleon. I should remember those.
PART.1: I should learn more vocabulary ... before...
PART.2: We should have like a kids book. Animals, like, colors.
PART.1: Before, the guy had a beer and the first question was asking if it.
PART.2: A bear.
PART.1: A bear and it was saying if the mother has milk or not and I was like...
He knows the word for it and I was like what is it.
PART.1: He was describing it and I was like I have no idea.
Another question was another question was like. Does it have a tail?
I think a small one but I'm not sure about it.
PART.2: I think a small one.
PART.1: And does it sleep in the winter?
PART.2: I think yeah.
PART.1: Same. I was also like guessing. But I was always like take another question, I have no idea.