PART.1: What it even is? Is it a horse or a donkey?
PART.2: I think it's a cow because...
PART.1: I can see the boobie.
PART.2: Okay, let's check. Number 1.
PART.1: Where are the boobies? Ah! I found the boobies.
PART.2: We need this one first... It's an eight-piece thing.
PART.1: That's it.
PART.2: Perfect.
PART.2: Then, we need a four-piece, this one. And a two-piece, this one.
PART.1: Mmm.
PART.2: Here.
PART.2: In English, please.
PART.1: Oh, yeah, true. Ah! The other way.
PART.2: Now...
PART.1: Eh...
PART.2: The hell is that?
PART.1: Ah, it's this one, I think.
PART.2: ...I think so.
PART.1: I'm gonna... Like that.
PART.2: Yes, with the .... down. Perfect.
PART.1: This one.
PART.2: One, two, three, four, five, six, a twelve one.
PART.2: Twelve?
PART.1: Here.
PART.1: I was like...
PART.2: And that goes on top.
PART.1: Completely? Yeah.
PART.2: Next.
PART.2: Another four one...
PART.2: And two fours...
PART.2: And this one in the middle.
PART.1: We should maybe think of getting lego.
PART.2: Yeah, definitely! This is so fun.
PART.1: It is really more fun than I remember.
PART.2: What does that mean?
PART.1: Those are the titties.
PART.2: One titty...
PART.1: But the titties have to be upwards.
PART.2: What?
PART.2: Oh, they go into these small things, I think.
PART.2: But, how the hell?
PART.2: This, with this open side up...
PART.1: Be careful with your finger.
PART.1: Ah! Yeah, I just pushed it in.
PART.2: And a cow has four boobies.
PART.2: And the rest of the experiment is just me like changing shit off this thing...
PART.2: Oh, this one doesn't fit.
PART.2: And then...
PART.1: Oh, they also have purple boobie.
PART.2: They have small eyes, they're so cute. Okay, concentration.
PART.2: We need two flat ones.
PART.1: Two flat ones. Here's another one.
PART.2: And...
PART.1: And, two hollow here.
PART.1: And these are supposed to be the legs, I suppose.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: That's all...
PART.2: And that's all.
PART.1: I love it already.
PART.2: Same!
PART.2: Okay. Another one of these, another one of these, two eyes.... Do you wanna make a winky face?
PART.1: Two eyes...
PART.1: Don't take too big ones of these, it's too big, no?
PART.2: Okay.
PART.2: And what is that weird thing? It's this one.
PART.1: Yeah, I think so too.
PART.2: We need two of those...
PART.1: Ah, that's supposed to be the head!
PART.1: Got ya!
PART.2: Can you see another one of these?
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: ...that one.
PART.2: This...And then put this, like...
PART.1: On this one.
PART.2: And this like so...
PART.2: PERSONA A y B: Blue eyes.
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.2: I love this so much.
PART.1: It's great.
PART.2: Wait, what the fuck? Why do we have to put it down?
PART.1: Ah... Yes.
PART.2: Ah... I have to put it like this.
PART.2: It's almost done!
PART.1: I think it actually is done... We're done with the eyes... Ah, no, come on.
PART.2: Really?
PART.1: So, the top with more hair.
PART.2: Emma!
PART.2: You just killed the cow!
PART.2: We need two of those flat ones, I can't find the other one.
PART.1: I'm confused.
PART.2: You have to put it on the back, yeah.
PART.1: We need another flat one, right?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: I can't see it. Ah! Here.
PART.2: And then the small tiny ears... Ah! They're so cute!
PART.1: One... Ah! These are ears too, now I understand.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: I understand!
PART.1: I understand!
PART.2: Okay!
PART.1: Oh, that's so cute!
PART.2: Can we call him Bobby?
PART.1: Bobby?
PART.2: Bobby.
PART.1: Bobby it is. I think Bobby should actually have a little purple hair, if we're done.
PART.1: Oh, look, we're done! He just needs a little bit more to eat.
PART.2: Punk as fuck! Okay, I'll just take it out.
PART.1: What's the Marge...?
PART.2: Oh, no, we have to put the... the...
PART.1: From Simpsons? Marge Simpsons?
PART.2: Marge Simpson?
PART.1: What's her name, weird name?
PART.2: Marge Simpson.
PART.1: I take that back, it's not weird, it's beautiful.
PART.1: Here.
PART.2: Ah.
PART.2: I think it's cute if it stands there.
PART.1: We don't... We put it down there?
PART.2: I don't know, that would be cute if it's like standing there eating.
PART.1: Okay, but, do you think he would mind if he looks like a punk?
PART.2: As if it were mine!
PART.2: Just put it, if he doesn't like we can take it out... Oops! Emma!
PART.2: Perfect!
PART.1: Love it!
PART.2: Should we scream?
PART.2: He doesn't have a..., that's so sad!
PART.1: True, and he didn't even use the...
PART.2: Do you wanna use it?
PART.1: Brrrrr!
PART.2: That was a... cow.
PART.2: Okay, I think we did... I think we did well.
PART.1: Oh, my God. Sun, do you see this?
PART.2: Yes!
PART.1: Ka-ching!
PART.2: Ka-ching! Are there more flowers? Maybe we can put them around, or something... It would be really nice.
PART.1: I think this is a flower.
PART.2: We'll make it a flower.
PART.1: There's more green... Ah! Look, there's something yellow.
PART.2: I really wanna make her winking, I'm gonna make her winking.
PART.1: Ah, okay.
PART.2: So cute.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.2: I think our...
PART.1: They wrote "Lego" on this like the small as possible.
PART.2: What even is that? Is that supposed to be the tail? No, whatever. We're done.
PART.1: Javi!
PART.2: Look a this! It's so tiny!