PART.2: You want to go first?
PART.1: My heartbeat is going on.
PART.1: This is the hardest game.
PART.1: Ok, this one.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: You are winning already, ok.
PART.2: Oh, yes!
PART.1: Is it?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: No!
PART.2: No! It's this!
PART.1: It's the mouse,
I think you get it.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: And now me.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: I should have it...
PART.2: Oh, sorry, sorry.
PART.1: No, it's your turn.
PART.1: I am getting sloopy.
PART.2: Yes, yes, yes.
PART.2: It is your turn.
PART.1: I think is a good game,
I should get it.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: That one?
PART.1: I like to hide the cards.
PART.1: No, no!
PART.1: It's your turn?
PART.1: Yes!
PART.2: You take it, yes.
PART.1: But it is a bit effort
because it's closer to me anyway.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: But it is a bit effort
because it's closer to me anyway.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: Yes, your turn.
PART.1: I think so.
PART.1: So you got it.
PART.1: Now it's your turn again.
PART.1: That one.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: It's yours.
PART.1: And the last one.
PART.1: That's the bottle, no!
PART.1: No! That one!
PART.2: Why I went to this one??
PART.1: We went both
for the wrong ones.
PART.2: Its yours.
PART.1: We went both
for the wrong ones.
PART.2: Its yours.
PART.1: He didn't explain,
I don't know,
PART.1: he didn't explain the rules
the first time
PART.1: and what happens if you take
the wrong one?
PART.2: I guess is like who picks
the right one first.
PART.1: I don't know,
I asked my friend
PART.1: and she is like it becomes
like the other person's turn.
PART.1: And you just have to wait,
I guess, but is like he wins anyway.
PART.1: Anyway...
PART.1: So, let's see.
PART.2: I think I've lost.
PART.1: I think you won,
maybe, I don't know.
PART.2: I think I've lost.
PART.1: I think you won,
maybe, I don't know.
PART.2: I have three, five!
PART.1: I got six.
PART.1: Not the first,
when I played maybe
I shouldn't tell you?
PART.1: I don't know.
PART.2: You played in the past this game?
PART.1: The session before this.
PART.2: Yes, I also did.
PART.1: When I played with my friend
she was really bad at it
PART.1: to the point that I was like just
waiting for her to pick the right one.
PART.2: Yes, I also did.
PART.1: When I played with my friend
she was really bad at it
to the point
PART.1: that I was like just
waiting for her to pick the right one.
PART.1: Come on!
Just pick the correct one!
PART.1: But it is a nice game,
I don't know how is it called.
PART.2: In the last one,
for some reason,
PART.2: there was this blue book
a lot of times so I was always
looking for the blue book.
PART.1: Always!
SUPERVISOR: How was it?