PART.1: Ok.
PART.2: What should we talk about?
PART.1: Actually, I brought
the ping pong rackets
but we are not going to have time
to play after this.
PART.2: Yes, not really.
PART.1: But did you go play last weekend?
PART.2: Yes, I went on Sunday
and we were playing volleyball,
but on Saturday I did play.
PART.1: But did you go play last weekend?
PART.2: Yes, I went on Sunday
and we were playing volleyball,
but on Saturday I did play.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Also on Friday evening.
PART.1: Yes, we could sometimes go
like after but these Saturdays
are for me supercomplicated.
PART.2: Yes, so normally we can play
until the sunset
which is at 10pm or 9pm.
PART.2: Yes, so normally we can play
until the sunset
which is at 10pm or 9pm.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: So, sometimes we are playing
in Ciutadella or in Barceloneta
from 7pm or 6pm
until 8pm or 8:30pm.
PART.1: Yes, after work?
PART.2: Yes, after work.
PART.1: But you guys
are always going to Ciutadella?
PART.2: It is good to go there
because it is a bit covered
and it helps and is less windy.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: But it is also too crowded,
that's a big problem
PART.2: and sometimes we have to wait
for like an hour before we can play
unless we are lucky
PART.2: and we know someone
who is already playing
and let us join.
PART.2: But it is also too crowded,
that's a big problem
PART.2: and sometimes we have to wait
for like an hour before we can play
unless we are lucky
PART.2: and we know someone
who is already playing
and let us join.
PART.2: Otherwise, there are not
a lot of good places, I mean,
not all tables are even
or some tables are broken.
PART.1: Yes, I really like the La Placídia.
PART.2: Placídia, yes,
but the problem is
that always is quite windy
for some reason I don't know.
PART.1: Yes, I really like the La Placídia.
PART.2: Placídia, yes,
but the problem is
that always is quite windy
for some reason I don't know.
PART.1: I know is full of kids as well.
PART.2: Placídia, yes,
but the problem is
that always is quite windy
for some reason I don't know.
PART.1: I know is full of kids as well.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: I sometimes too like
that table is close
to your current office
PART.1: and sometimes we could go there
to play after work
PART.1: and meet the others
and have a drink or something.
PART.2: Yes, that could be nice.
PART.1: And then see,
this week is really crazy for me
and I think next we as well
until I come back from Paris.
PART.2: You are going to Paris?
PART.1: I am going
for like four days for work.
PART.2: You are going to Paris?
PART.1: I am going
for like four days for work.
PART.2: Ah, for work.
PART.1: From the 1st until 4th
and maybe we do this camping weekend.
PART.2: Yes, I'll wait
until I decide if I go to work or not.
PART.1: Yes, yes, yes.
PART.2: Yes, I'll wait
until I decide if I go to work or not.
PART.1: I mean,
I'd probably actually go
like the post weekend
PART.1: because our friends
can only go the first weekend
PART.1: and the other people
I think they prefer the next weekend
so maybe we'll end up going
PART.1: I mean,
I'd probably actually go
like the post weekend
PART.1: because our friends
can only go the first weekend
and the other people
I think they prefer the next weekend
PART.2: Two weeks.
PART.1: But I don't mind
because it is not very far,
it is close to Plaza del Mar
and it is like supernice.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: We have the tent
and we have everything for it
except car, so...
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: We have the tent
and we have everything for it
except car, so...
PART.2: Do we need
to bring things there for camping
or how does this holiday work?
PART.1: Yes, it has also cabins,
like wooden houses.
PART.2: Do we need
to bring things there for camping
or how does this holiday work?
PART.1: Yes, it has also cabins,
like wooden houses.
PART.2: I mean, I would prefer
to bring my own stuff.
PART.1: No, we are going
to go with tents.
PART.2: You will bring your own tent?
PART.1: Yes, so you can rent parcels
and then in every parcel,
PART.1: I think there's a limited
amount of tents that can fit
PART.1: and it is important to resolve
because it is in high season.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: Yes, so you can rent parcels
and then in every parcel,
PART.1: I think there's a limited
amount of tents that can fit
PART.1: and it is important to resolve
because it is in high season.
PART.1: Yes, so you can rent parcels
and then in every parcel,
PART.1: I think there's a limited
amount of tents that can fit
PART.1: and it is important to resolve
because it is in high season.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: And it is like important
to know how many people
want to go and how many tents
PART.1: and then we just resolve
the parcels and places.
PART.2: But is it like in the nature
or is it like you don't feel
you are in the nature
and you are just inside or open...?
PART.1: In the nature,
it is in the nature.
PART.2: But is it like in the nature
or is it like you don't feel
you are in the nature
and you are just inside or open...?
PART.1: In the nature,
it is in the nature.
PART.2: Open space?
PART.1: The camping is next to the beach,
it has a private access
to some small base
PART.1: and then you go up to the camping
area and some spots have like a view
to the see.
PART.1: The camping is next to the beach,
it has a private access
PART.1: to some small base
and then you go up
to the camping area
PART.1: and some spots have
like a view to the see.
PART.1: The camping is next to the beach,
it has a private access
to some small base
PART.2: Oh, nice.
PART.1: It it very nice that camping
and also the bathrooms
are working nice, so...
PART.2: I mean, if we are there,
I would like also to go
for snorkling.
PART.1: I know, actually,
we were snorkling there.
PART.2: But I want to try
snorkling in the night,
I have never tried it
but I would love to.
PART.1: Yes, I mean,
I think it is possible to do it
if you have headlight.
PART.2: Yes, I can buy a headlight.
PART.1: Honestly,
it would maybe freak me out
because thinking the kind of animals
that there are there at night...
PART.2: Yes, I can buy a headlight.
PART.1: Honestly,
it would maybe freak me out
because thinking the kind of animals
that there are there at night...
PART.2: Yes, think that normally
all the animals
PART.2: that are there in the night
and not during the day
dont's see much.
PART.1: Honestly,
it would maybe freak me out
because thinking the kind of animals
PART.2: Yes, think that normally
all the animals
that are there in the night
PART.2:  and not during the day
dont's see much.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Yes, think that normally
all the animals
PART.2: that are there in the night
and not during the day
dont's see much.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.1: I saw people
sport fishing in the night.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: And very close to the...
PART.1: If you want to fish...
PART.2: Maybe I don't want to fish
but I want to see what is there.
PART.1: If you want to fish...
PART.2: Maybe I don't want to fish
but I want to see what is there.
PART.1: I know, actually, last year
when we were there
it was one of the highest demand
PART.1: and varieties of fish
I've seen in the Costa Brava
only around the shore,
PART.1: there's like a big rock
close to the shore
PART.1: I mean, there were
like more than what we usually see.
PART.2: But is it too cold in the night
or is it the same like the day?
PART.2: Because when I went in
the summer I saw people wearing full
of this new brand suits,
so maybe it is cold.
PART.1: No, I think it was not cold
but it was kind of bad
when we arrived
on Friday last year
PART.1: because there was a huge storm
and luckily it was over
after ten minutes.
PART.2: Because when
PART.1: No, I think it was not cold
but it was kind of bad
when we arrived
on Friday last year
PART.1: because there was a huge storm
and luckily it was over
after ten minutes.
PART.2: Oh...
PART.1: No, I think it was not cold
but it was kind of bad
when we arrived
on Friday last year
PART.1: because there was a huge storm
and luckily it was over
after ten minutes.
PART.1: No, I think it was not cold
but it was kind of bad
when we arrived
on Friday last year
PART.1: because there was a huge storm
and luckily it was over
after ten minutes.
PART.1: And then it was not raining
for the rest of the weekend
but it was like superstressful
PART.1: because we had to set up the tent,
it was getting late
and it was getting dark,
PART.1: but it was also in September
and the days were already shorter
PART.2: And how did you manage
the food and the bathroom?
PART.1: They have a lot of baths,
so they have like a big building
that's like a bathrooms building
and showers for both genders.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: They have a lot of baths,
so they have like a big building
that's like a bathrooms building
and showers for both genders.
PART.1: They have a lot of baths,
so they have like a big building
that's like a bathrooms building
and showers for both genders.
PART.1: And they have
a restaurant on the beach
and we also buy something
and we just eat it in the morning.
PART.2: Nice.
PART.1: So, it wasn't necessary.
PART.2: So you like
buying food over there
in the restaurant?
PART.1: We were eating at the restaurant
and we were buying food
that was like for breakfast
like bread or something.
PART.2: Yes, yes, ok.
PART.1: We were eating at the restaurant
and we were buying food
that was like for breakfast
like bread or something.
PART.1: We were eating at the restaurant
and we were buying food
that was like for breakfast
like bread or something.
PART.1: It was nice, I mean,
but I know I want to go for a night
PART.1: because we went for two nights
and two nights in camping
can be too much.
PART.2: Too much, ok.