PART.2: Yeah, yeah.
PART.1: Who is going to
start first?
PART.2: You can start.
PART.1: Ok...So, the first
question.
PART.1: Is this animal a mammal?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Not a mammal.
PART.2: It's not a mammal, no.
PART.2: My question.
PART.2: We have to keep a track of
questions.
PART.1: Maybe it's better we
finish, I finishthen you start
PART.1: Cos maybe we lose the track
of the questions...
PART.1: I don't know.
PART.2: It's a suggestion.
PART.2: Yes. Of course.
PART.1: In the previous one...
it was better.
PART.2: Perfect.
PART.1: So.
PART.1: It's not a mammal.
PART.1: Is it a bird?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Not a bird.
PART.1: Is it a kind of fish?
PART.2: Uh huh. No.
PART.1: So.
PART.1: Is it a kind of
animals who can live both in water.
PART.1: I don't know the name in English.
PART.2: They can live like water
and outside.
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Like crocodiles or those
species?
PART.2: Reptiles?
PART.2: Something like reptiles.
PART.2: No...It doesn't.
PART.2: No. It's not.
PART.1: Or turtles or so?
PART.2: Yeah...
PART.2: I got your idea but no.
PART.1: It's not that.
PART.1: What other types of species
we have?
PART.1: No mammal, no bird, no fish.
PART.1: Perhaps it's a kind of insect?
PART.2: Er?
PART.1: Animal? Insect is not an
animal.
PART.2: No.
PART.1: I think it's not
really in the...
PART.1: Catagories.
PART.1: I'm stuck a little....
PART.1: It's not a bird.
PART.1: It's not a mammal...it's not.
PART.2: It's difficult...
PART.1: It's difficult
PART.1: Yes.
PART.1: If I find the catagory...
PART.2: Yeah, then you can...
move.
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.2: You go like...straight.
PART.1: Yeah, a few questions.
PART.1: I can say what it is.
PART.1: It's tough...
PART.2: To me...this game is the
worst.
PART.2: It's hard.
PART.1: Previous time I was
quite near but I couldn't find the
animal but I was quite near.
PART.1: They have five species of
animals.
PART.1: I selected four of them,
except the insects which are not
animals, they have five.
PART.1: if I'm not wrong...
PART.2: One of your questions
like livein the water and outside it
doesn't...it's not water.
PART.2: But it can be like....
close to that species.
PART.1: I got it, I got it. So.
PART.1: Does it have any hands or foots?
PART.2: You mean...
PART.1: Can it run?
PART.2: Yes, yes. Yes.
PART.2: It goes.
PART.1: It has arm and legs?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: So I have six...
PART.1: Is it...
PART.1: Do we have the skin of the
colour kind of green... or so so?
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.1: So I have green...
PART.1: Is it a frog?
PART.2: No.
PART.2: Not a frog, but it's familiar
to a frog,
but it's not a frog.
PART.1: Ah. Those...
PART.1: But it can live in the water...
PART.2: Yes, but if I have that
other question I would say yes...
PART.2: Then no.
PART.2: With this one, no.
PART.2: No.
PART.1: So it's not living in
the water...
PART.2: Its colour.
PART.2: In terms of the colour it's like
green.
PART.2: But it can have other colours
as well.
PART.2: But...mainly green.
PART.2: But it may change.
PART.1: Maybe I can guess.
PART.1: Is this animal can change
the colour of the skin?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: So I know what it is....
but I don't know the name.
PART.1: The one that has two eyes here
that can move... in different
directions.
PART.1: Also the...
PART.1: It has a very long tongue
that can...
PART.2: Uh huh.
PART.2: That's the one,
yeah.
PART.2: You got it.
PART.2: Just open it, yeah.
PART.1: And I got one!
PART.1: What is the name?
PART.1: Chameleon?
PART.2: Chameleon?
PART.2: They say 'chameleon'
or chameleon...
PART.2: In Portuguese we say 'camaleao'.
PART.2: In Spanish like I think
it's ike 'cameleon'.
PART.2: Something like that.
PART.1: OK.
PART.2: But the skin was a very
very important part of the animal...
PART.2: OK so I have to start with
mine then...
PART.2: Alright so....erm.
PART.2: Friend of mine...these animal.
PART.2: Do we usually eat...humans.
PART.1: No. No.
PART.2: No. People don't eat.
PART.2: Do we find it in the zoo?
PART.1: Kind of...
PART.1: Not all zoos...but, yes...
PART.1: Some zoos, yes.
PART.2: Some zoos, yes.
PART.2: OK.
PART.2: Does it fly?
PART.1: No
PART.2: No
PART.2: Is it a mammal?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Is...is bigger than
a human?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: No.
PART.2: Mammal...
PART.2: Does it have a tail?
PART.1: I can't say it has
but not that long.
PART.1: It's a short...
PART.1: I don't know.
PART.2: It's like...
PART.2: OK.
PART.1: Or maybe no...because...
PART.1: I never see ....tail but...
PART.1: Maybe something similar to tail
but very small.
PART.1: PERSONA B.: Just like it's not
something important then.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: Er...
PART.2: Does it has like different
colours?
PART.2: Or just like one very specific?
PART.1: I think no.
PART.1: I just saw one colour in this...
PART.1: in this animal.
PART.2: Does it live like
in...in four.
PART.2: Four...er... tai...not tail.
PART.2: Like this...in four...
PART.1: It can but it mainly do
not do that...
PART.1: It can... but...
PART.1: He doesn't use to do like this
but he...it can.
PART.1: It's tough one...
PART.2: Let's see...so.
PART.2: It's a mammal...
PART.2: We don't eat...
PART.2: What else....
PART.2: Does it live in the forest?
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.1: Kind of... yeah.
PART.1: On trees.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: I have one more
question, right?
PART.2: Does he eat like nuts?
PART.1: I don't know what it
eats.
PART.2: You know just like these
small nuts?
PART.2: Or it's not...
PART.1: I don't really know what
it eats but you can change your
question.
PART.2: OK.
PART.2: Let me see then.
PART.2: Does it have like long feathers?
PART.2: A lot of like... er.
PART.1: It's not long...it's
normal.
PART.2: Just like short?
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.1: Like this short
maybe.
PART.1: Not very long.
PART.2: OK.
PART.2: I'm gonna take a chance.
PART.2: It's like a racoon or something?
PART.2: Or a racoon or like a "skirel"?
PART.2: Or those kind of animals?
PART.1: I don't say it's
like a racoon but...
PART.1: It's similar to racoon.
PART.1: But it's not racoon or...
PART.1: The behaviour is not like a
racoon...but... it's similar.
PART.2: OK.
PART.1: It's bigger than a
racoon.
PART.2: It's bigger.
PART.1: And also I think that
racoons can hunt.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.1: But this one I think no.
PART.2: No.
PART.2: OK.
PART.2: Can't think...
PART.2: It's bigger than a racoon...
PART.2: Last question.
PART.2: It's not a reptile?
PART.2: Nothing about...no other, no.
PART.2: Far from that.
PART.2: I'm thinking something about
like between a racoon and a bear.
PART.2: I was like trying to find
an animal...
PART.1: But both of them can
hunt; this one no.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.1: I told it was living on
trees...
PART.1: I can give you a guide.
PART.1: You can find it...
PART.1: It's not all over the world,
it's just in a part of the world.
PART.2: Right.
PART.2: And probably it's very specific
to one part of the world?
PART.2: And people know that.
PART.2: They know
it's from that specific part...
PART.2: They like...
PART.2: Kinda like these Tasmanian
animal...or something.
PART.1: It's not living there.
PART.2: No.
PART.1: If I say...
PART.1: I can say...
PART.1: It's living in Australia.
PART.1: I think now it's quite easy.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: That's.
PART.2: But I don't know the
name in English.
PART.2: A kangaroo or something?
PART.1: No.
PART.1: It's not a kanagaroo.
PART.1: Because kangaroo can hunt...
PART.2: Can hunt...
PART.1: It's big also.
PART.2: It's bigger.
PART.2: But yes.
PART.2: I know what it is.
PART.2: It is a koala.
PART.1: Exactly.
PART.2: Then.
PART.2: It was like too many questions.
PART.2: It was like yeah, a koala.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: It was very specific. Yeah.
PART.1: It's really hard.
PART.1: I think this one was harder
than this.
PART.2: Uh huh.
PART.2: Yeah, yeah.
PART.2: Should we...
PART.2: Call 'em?
PART.2: We're here...
PART.2: Koala...
PART.2: My first one was a fish.
PART.2: A dolphin.
PART.2: It was a dolphin.
PART.2: And today.
PART.2: No.
PART.2: First one I did
two interactions.
PART.2: It was a dolphin and a bear.
PART.2: And I was able to find the
dolphin but it was like easy....
PART.2: Dolphin and bear...was like easy.
PART.2: But the other one was... a bird.
PART.2: A bird that I have never heard
of.
PART.2: And this.
PART.2: But Meysam, when you did what was
the...the other animal?
PART.1: Mine was...bison