PART.2: This is it
and we can start forward
with the blue one and then orange.
PART.1: Is this one? I think so.
PART.1: Yes, it's this one.
PART.1: So, we are starting
with the piece of blue.
PART.2: Then the yellow...
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: And then more...
PART.2: Another yellow?
PART.2: This one?
PART.2: Or is it orange?
PART.1: I don't know,
there's another yellow here also.
PART.2: Yes, because on top
I think the first one
is orange and then yellow.
PART.1: Maybe, of course one orange
and the two yellow above.
PART.1: But in the other way.
PART.2: Oh, yes, that's true.
PART.1: And we need two more yellow
and here is one.
PART.1: Maybe that one?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Cool, now we know one...
PART.2: Then grey.
PART.1: Yes, a small grey one.
PART.1: I don't know,
is it grey or is it black?
PART.1: I saw one black.
PART.2: It could be a black, yes-
PART.1: And then with this blue?
PART.2: But there's like a grey one with...
PART.2: Just the black
and the grey, yes.
PART.1: I think it's that one.
PART.2: Yes, it's this.
PART.1: Ok, this blue.
PART.2: Is it also in the station?
No, here.
PART.1: Yes, and then I think
there is this one and it's too
small!
PART.2: But...
PART.1: Ah, and the other one.
PART.2: Exactly, yes.
PART.2: It goes like this, yes.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: That's it,
do you want to do another one?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Which one do you want?
PART.2: The first one?
PART.1: The first one?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: Ok, I don't know what it is.
PART.1: Starting with a brown.
PART.2: This.
PART.1: Brown six
and then maybe that one?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Then another one brown?
I think this one.
PART.2: Ok, it's like on the other side.
PART.2: Is it round like this?
PART.1: Yes and then the other one
it is not rounded.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: Yes and then the other one
it is not rounded.
PART.1: Which I think is this one.
PART.1: And then a green weird thing.
PART.1: Maybe this?
PART.2: Yes, this.
PART.1: But no,
we have a brown first
so always keep this.
PART.2: Yes, the small brown.
PART.1: In the middle,
this one goes in the middle.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: And then you have this green
on one side of the...
PART.2: But the first here,
the light brown goes on top.
PART.1: And then you have this green
on one side of the...
PART.2: But the first here,
the light brown goes on top.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: This one before the green?
PART.1: This one, yes.
PART.1: I think it was on top of the brown
but maybe it wasn't neither.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: I don't know which one goes.
PART.2: Oh, very difficult.
PART.1: Oh, we have to put this away.
PART.2: Yes, that's true.
PART.1: And now another weird one
looking brown.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Yes, I think.
PART.1: Yes, just put it on top.
PART.1: Of the second half.
PART.2: On the other side, yes?
PART.2: Yes, it's like this.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.1: And then we have one green
and another brown, maybe that one.
SUPERVISOR: Hi!
PART.1: And then we have one green
and another brown, maybe that one.