PART.2: Then, what is your name?
PART.1: I'm Meysam. Meysam.
PART.2: Meysam.
PART.1: With 'M' at the end.
PART.1: I'm from Iran
PART.1: I'm thirty-six years old
PART.1: I'm doing research for a
long time here.
PART.1: Maybe it's now eight years.
PART.2: Eight years? So you're
living in Barcelona for 8 years?
PART.1: Yeah. Eight years.
PART.2: Erm...
PART.1: I don't know, you
can ask
PART.1: questions...I don't know what
to say.
PART.2: I can tell you my name
PART.2: My name is Irineo
PART.2: Well, it's not a common name
PART.2: I'm from Brazil
PART.2: So it's not a Brazilian name
PART.2: But it's easy to...to...
to remember
PART.2: because here they have like
the Pireneo's mountains
PART.2: right?
PART.2: so you just have to take
the 'P' out, the first letter
PART.2: and then you have  my name.
Like Irineo.
PART.2: So it's very easy for the Catalans
and for people here.
PART.1: s there any relationship
with the Pyrenees?
PART.2: I don't ...I don't know
PART.2: I don't have any idea.
PART.2: I think that the name is like
Rumanian
PART.2: or something like that,
I'm not sure.
PART.2: What I know is that I met
one guy which is Irineo
PART.2: in my life, which is my father.
PART.2: My father is Irineo as well
PART.2: Really?
PART.2: Yeah. So,  he's Irineo
and I'm Irineo junior,
PART.2: we have this in Brazil
PART.2: when you have the same name
as your father
PART.2: you put like 'junior'.
PART.1: I see Brazil,
PART.1: I see this is...
Portuguese...
PART.2: Might be, might be...
PART.1: The names are
like two lines
PART.2: Er...yeah
PART.1: Six or seven  different.
PART.2: Especially in Portugal.
I have a friend in Portugal
PART.2: that has a long names,
PART.2: like four last names
PART.2: and it's a mess.
PART.2: But I have just one last name
but my family is actually
PART.2: from Italy.
PART.2: Coz like my grand-grand-fathers
they left Italy
PART.2: and they went to Brazil. This was
very normal like 150 years ago...
PART.2: more or less
PART.2: when a lot of Italians they
left Europe
PART.2: to go to South America
PART.1: Because of resources
or...
PART.2: Yeah...because they
have like...
PART.2: they were agricultors and
they have a lot of land there
PART.2: it was like land with no peoples
...no...so they went there
PART.2: to work in the land.
PART.2: So  the Brazilian government and
also the Argentinian, the Uruguayan
PART.2: I think that they gave like land
for them to produce
PART.2: so then they came to Brazil.
PART.2: So that's why we have a lot of
Germans, Italians, Polish like in
PART.2: the...in South America
PART.2: but especially in Argentina
and Brazil.
PART.2: So my last name is actually
from Italy.
PART.2: It's like Savignano
PART.1: Um...
PART.2: And I've been here
for two and a half years
PART.2: I came here to make my Master
PART.2: and then I'm just like,I'm working
out like this last year at least.
PART.1: So you are working?
PART.2:  Yes, I'm working now.
PART.1: You abandoned research?
PART.2: Not research.
PART.2: I'm not from the academic world,
no.
PART.2: I just like work...like normal.
PART.2: I ...My company is at the
Torre Agbar.
PART.2: You know the Torre Agbar?
PART.2: Like the colours and stuff?
PART.2: Yeah. I work there. Inside.
PART.2: So I work for an internet
company. Yeah.
PART.1: Your field is Computer
Science?
PART.2: No, not Computer Science
I studied Business Administration.
PART.2: So I have a friend that is I think
is like part of the study and that's why I'm here
PART.2: but I'm not a researcher...no,
I don't have have any idea of all
PART.2: these cameras do...is like...
PART.1: But in business is there
any  PhD or that...?
PART.2: Yeah. Yes. There are
PhDs in business.Yeah.
PART.2: Um...I did my Master in Project
Management.
PART.2: So that like basically you learn
how to manage a project...all that
PART.2: to work with things...
PART.2: but yeah, of course, there are
like PhDs in this area...as....
PART.2: as jobs....because then you can mix
like economics with business and
PART.2: even math. You can do like
mathematics with business
PART.2: and all that. You can apply
different fields.
PART.1: I think this field is
one of thegood opportunities
PART.2: Uh hu...um...
PART.2: to take jobs, I think...
PART.2: Yeah I think it changes a lot.
It's very dynamic.
PART.1: It depends on the
economy
PART.2: Exactly...
PART.2: If the economy is down, you go down
as well.
PART.2: So it's very...it's like....
it's not a stable job
PART.1: I think it's quite
common for all the jobs with
PART.1: respect to the economy. If the
economy goes down everybody go down
PART.2: Yeah...it's true
PART.1: In Computer Science for
instance nobody is going to invest.
PART.2: That's right.
PART.1: in Artificial Intelligence
PART.1: then everybody is going to lose
jobs. It's because you need to sell
PART.1: the product...and if the
economy goes down...
PART.1: Right. Definitely...
PART.1: The company can not
pay you...yeah