PART.2: So you start then.
PART.1: Yes, we can do two things:
or I ask all the time
until I finish and you do your game,
or we can do one question,
one question, one question...
PART.2: No, the first one.
PART.1: The first one, ok.
PART.1: So, about my question,
about my animal,
do I live most of the time
in the water? In the sea?
In the river? Water?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Am I big?
PART.2: Big is not very accurate.
PART.2: Think that a bear is big.
PART.1: Small.
PART.2: Big, bear is small?
PART.1: Ah, I understood beer.
PART.2: No, bear, bear.
PART.1: No, that's medium.
PART.2: Bear is medium,
comparing to bird
it is not big.
PART.1: But neither small,
it is medium then.
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Small.
PART.2: If bear is medium...
PART.1: Then this is small.
PART.1: It is small.
PART.1: Ok, two questions, no?
PART.1: Do I live along
or with small family
or with a plenty of family?
PART.2: How can I answer this
with yes or no?
PART.1: Do I live in big communities?
PART.2: Big communities this animal?
Some race of this animal yes
but I am not sure
about this exact animal.
PART.2: Let's say yes.
PART.1: Do I live in the open sea?
PART.2: Open sea?
PART.2: Sometimes but not sea,
more in the lakes.
PART.1: More in the lakes...
PART.2: Somehow.
PART.2: But near water.
PART.1: Do I put eggs
to have my kids?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Yes?
PART.1: Eggs?
PART.1: Yes, but...
PART.1: Am I an "anfibio"?
PART.2: What?
PART.1: Anfibio, do you know
what it is an anfibio?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Anfibio is something,
I don't know the word in English,
it is like I live in the water,
but I used to be also outside,
whatever.
PART.2: When you ask open sea,
you mean inside water?
PART.1: No, open sea
is like open ocean.
PART.1: Like far away,
not near the beach or...
PART.2: No, no, no.
PART.1: Anfibio means like,
you know the turtles?
La rana como se dice?
PART.1: The animal that jumps
that can be in the water
and out of the water?
PART.1: All this kind of animals.
PART.1: Google Translator?
Google Translator.
PART.2: Anfibia?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: No, it's not anfibio.
PART.1: No?
PART.1: Ups, then I am...
PART.1: Ups...
PART.1: Ah, my friend...
PART.1: Am I from the reptile family?
PART.2: Reptile, reptile, reptile...
PART.1: It is like...
PART.2: No.
PART.1: No?
PART.2: No, reptile no.
PART.1: Are you sure?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Crocodile is a reptile, eh?
PART.2: Yes, I know, I know.
PART.1: Wow, I don't know then.
PART.1: Open sea, so it is more like
I am in a sweet water,
sweet water.
PART.2: But it is not inside water.
PART.1: Eh?
PART.2: It is not inside water,
it is near water.
PART.2: She needs to be near water.
PART.1: It needs to be near...
PART.1: But I am kind of small...
PART.1: And I put eggs?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Eggs? But I am not a turtle?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: And I put eggs
but I don't live inside there,
but very close...
PART.1: I am not a crocodile.
Eggs?
PART.1: A crab...
PART.1: Ok, I only have one question.
PART.1: More in lakes...
PART.1: Near the water...
PART.1: I put eggs.
PART.1: Do I have...
PART.1: Hair covering my body?
PART.2: Hair no.
PART.1: Crab?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Ostras...
PART.1: Es verdad...
PART.2: You forgot to ask
if it is flying...
PART.1: Yes! I should have asked!
Ok, your turn.
PART.2: Even it is flying,
but how you can say
it is a pelican or it is other...?
PART.1: Yes! It is difficult!
Maybe never!
Ok, go ahead.
PART.2: Among 40 animals...
PART.1: Yes, I don't know.
PART.2: Ok, let's say.
PART.2: Is it mammal?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: A mammal.
PART.2: Is it big?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Big, bigger than bear.
PART.2: What option!
PART.1: Yes!
PART.2: Is it kind of blue the color?
PART.1: Kind of blue?
PART.2: Yes, like not this blue but...
PART.1: No, no.
PART.2: The tone or the color
similar to blue.
PART.1: No.
PART.2: No? Not at all?
PART.1: Not at all.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.2: Is it living inside water?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: How many questions?
PART.1: Four.
PART.2: Is it with a very long neck?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: So, it's big, not blue,
it's a mammal...
PART.2: And it's bigger than a bear.
PART.2: Ok...
PART.2: What animal you have bigger
than a bear?
PART.1: Mammal means that
no eggs no? For the kids?
PART.2: Yes, like humans.
PART.1: Yes, yes.
PART.2: Is it living in the...
PART.2: Ok, no, no,
you said the neck is not long.
PART.2: Do we drink its milk?
PART.1: The humans?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: No.
PART.2: It is not a cow.
PART.2: Does it have horn? Like?
PART.2: A horn.
PART.1: Yes, but not here,
like this, in that way.
PART.2: Is it a kind of moose?
PART.1: What is moose?
PART.2: Oh, I should...
PART.1: No.
PART.2: How many do I have?
PART.1: Still two questions
and then you can say the animal.
PART.2: Still two questions...
PART.2: It has horns...
PART.2: It doesn't have long neck...
PART.2: And it is bigger than a bear.
PART.2: Is it living in the jungle
or in the desert?
PART.1: None of them.
PART.2: So, in the mountain then.
PART.1: Well, in any case,
a little bit closer
to the second case.
PART.2: Desert.
PART.2: Is it a camel?
PART.1: No.
PART.1: No? One question?
PART.2: No? One question?
PART.2: I don't know what is it.
PART.2: But a camel doesn't have horns.
PART.1: No.
PART.1: Last question.
PART.2: Last question...
PART.2: It is big...
PART.2: So...
PART.2: The horn is not here, is here,
so it is not an elephant.
PART.2: Because it is not blue,
because elephant is a kind of blue.
PART.2: That is why I asked.
PART.2: It doesn't have a very long neck,
which is a giraffe,
so it is not a giraffe.
PART.2: Because a giraffe has also horns.
PART.2: And those hasn't have a horn,
it is not a kind of moose...
PART.2: I don't know then what is it.
PART.1: Do a final question
to have more clues.
PART.2: Is it a kind of...
PART.1: You can surrender
if you have no more ideas.
PART.2: No more ideas.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.2: Ah, buffalo...
PART.1: Buffalo.
PART.2: Yes, buffalo.
PART.1: Well, this kind is bison,
but it is of the same family.
PART.2: But I was quite close...
PART.2: I didn't remember this type,
I mentioned cow
because...
PART.1: Yes!
PART.2: it is a kind of cow
but not exactly the cow.
PART.2: It is not moose.
PART.1: Yes, you were closer on whole.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: But it was also difficult that one.
PART.1: Mine was much more difficult.
PART.1: No? But this is not easy.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: I think this two ones
are from the hard category.
PART.1: Javi has the cards
in easy, medium and hard category
and I think these ones were
from the hard category.
PART.1: This is nice about this game.
PART.2: I think this is really good.
PART.1: But I didn't like
that you decided to surrender.
PART.1: You didn't want
to invest more effort.
PART.1: You said: I surrender.
PART.1: Why?