PART.2: So, I take one card
and if I win I keep the card?
PART.1: Yes, the one with more cards
at the end will win.
PART.1: Will win.
PART.1: Yes, the one with more cards
at the end will win.
PART.2: So, who starts?
PART.1: Please.
PART.2: So, you can see the card?
PART.1: Yes, yes, yes.
You should do that.
PART.2: So, blue is this one.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.2: For you or not?
PART.1: No, this is for you.
PART.1: Ok, I waited
to give you some advantage
because I know the game, ok?
PART.2: I know you are an expert
in this game.
PART.1: So, please focus
because I will be very competitive,
ok?
PART.2: No, you will win,
this is just my first...
PART.2: you will win,
PART.1: No, ok,
but please, go ahead.
PART.1: Ok? So please,
concentrate and be fast.
PART.1: Eh! This is not good.
PART.2: It's more near to you.
PART.1: Sometimes it will be closer to you,
my turn.
PART.2: Your turn, ok.
PART.2: Ah, ok.
PART.1: Exactly the same.
PART.2: The mouse?
PART.1: Yes, so this one is ok.
PART.1: This one, exactly the same.
PART.2: The ghost.
PART.1: But pick it!
You have to be fast.
PART.2: The ghost?
PART.1: But you have to pick it.
PART.1: Yes, the ghost.
PART.2: You were going to pick this one.
PART.1: I was doing like that.
PART.2: So, I should be like this.
PART.1: Yes, like that.
PART.1: This is the priority.
PART.2: Yes, this is the priority.
PART.2: I lost.
PART.2: This one.
PART.1: Very good.
PART.1: Ok, good job
for being the first time.
PART.1: Una, dos, tres, cuatro,
cinco, seis, siete, ocho... Yes.
PART.2: I am not very fast
in this kind of games.
PART.1: When you play a few times
at the end you know how to do that.
PART.1: This is a nice game.
PART.2: For kids I think this is perfect.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.1: And then, you need
to have cognitive abilities.
PART.2: When I was a kid
I used to do chess.
PART.1: We can play sometimes,
I am good.
PART.2: You are good?
PART.1: Yes, yes, I am good.
PART.2: Yes, it is a good idea.
PART.1: Yes, we can do that.