PART.1: Like a...
PART.2: It's a shoe?
PART.1: A shoe, I think so.
PART.1: Here we should have instructions.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.1: So, we have
to follow the instructions.
PART.1: Yes, these are the instructions,
so we have to start collecting.
PART.1: This is one, no?
PART.1: This is the other.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: This one?
PART.1: No.
PART.1: That one, yes.
PART.2: Is this?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.1: That way,
we need now the kind of flower.
PART.1: I don't know
what is that in pink.
PART.1: What is that color?
It should be pink.
PART.1: Or maybe this is the color?
Maybe this is the color no?
PART.2: This one.
PART.2: No.
PART.1: I think so.
PART.1: Very nice.
PART.1: Yes, maybe yes.
PART.2: There is no pink?
There are a lot of colors
but not pink.
PART.2: Yes, the color is different.
PART.1: It is different, right?
So yes, that is ok, good job.
PART.1: Do you want to do a complicated one?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: This one, maybe?
PART.1: There.
PART.2: This one?
PART.1: No.
PART.1: It is one, no?
PART.2: Yes, this one.
PART.1: Another one with this one.
PART.1: Here.
PART.1: Orange?
PART.1: The dark one.
PART.1: Two of these for what?
Ah, to put the...