PART.2: Where are you from?
PART.1: I am from Syria.
PART.2: Syria, yes.
PART.1: Yes and you are...?
PART.2: I am from Pakistan.
PART.1: Ah, welcome.
PART.1: You live here?
PART.2: Yes, yes.
PART.1: I live in Germany now,
I've been living there for two years
and I came here for vacations
PART.1: to visit my friend who was working
on this experiment
and she kind of sent me here.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: It is a kind of vacations, yes.
PART.1: What is your name?
PART.2: Farçat.
PART.1: Farçat, my name is Jessa.
PART.2: It is Jessa?
PART.1: Jessa, yes.
PART.2: Jessa, ok.
PART.1: What do you do?
PART.2: I am a computer research engineer,
I work here in a private company.
PART.1: Nice, I am a computer
scientist also as well.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: Nice, I am a computer
scientist also as well.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: I've just finished my masters
in distribution software systems
which maybe, I don't know,
it is not my biggest interest maybe.
PART.1: But anyway,
I just graduated from the master
like a month ago
and this is my vacation after.
PART.1: Like finishing the masters
and getting somewhere.
PART.1: Nice, it was nice
and it's really nice in Barcelona.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: You have been long here?
PART.2: Yes, I have been here
for the past eight years or more.
PART.1: Oh, nice and have you been
in other places?
PART.2: Yes, like in Spain or outside?
PART.2: Yes, I've been in Germany,
I've been living in Germany
for quite a while.
PART.2: Yes, I've been in Germany,
I've been living in Germany
for quite a while.
PART.1: Ah, also?
PART.2: I was living in Stuttgart
and I lived in Bochum
also for a while.
PART.1: Oh, you've been around a while.
PART.2: Yes, where do you live in Germany?
PART.1: Nice.
PART.1: In Frankfurt, near Frankfurt.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: In Darmstadt,
I don't know if you heard of it.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: In Darmstadt,
I don't know if you heard of it.
PART.2: I have been to Frankfurt, yes.
PART.1: Yes, Frankfurt is a really big city.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: It can be scary sometimes.
PART.1: Yes, it's nice.
PART.2: I think it is much colder
over there the weather.
PART.2: It is much cold
the weather over there.
PART.1: Not really, that city
is pretty hot in the summer.
PART.1: Now I think it is still colder
than here but I think
it is going to get also hotter.
PART.2: Yes, it will be much hotter.
PART.1: It's getting hotter everywhere.
PART.1: So, do you go to Pakistan?
PART.2: Yes, every year
I go once at least.
PART.1: Nice, do you have family here?
PART.2: No, I have
my parents in Pakistan
so go there to visit them.
PART.1: Yes, it is really nice.
PART.1: I also have
my parents in Syria still.
PART.2: Ok, where?
PART.1: In Damascus.
PART.2: In Damascus, ok.
PART.1: In the capital.
PART.1: Yes, I am going to see them
also this summer I am going there.
PART.1: Yes, to see how it goes.
PART.1: So, did you...?
Because now I've just
finished my masters
PART.1: and maybe you have some advice
to give me on what to do next
PART.1: because I was considering
if should I go for the PhD
but I am not so sure about it.
PART.2: So you did in distributed systems?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Is it more about networking?
PART.1: It is, but I am not
into networking, I mean,
PART.1: my thesis was in program analysis
using machine learning.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: Yes, I know a little
about machine learning.
PART.2: I would say
I would try to go for industry
at least a couple of years
of experience in industry,
PART.2: specially in Germany,
I think there's a lot of work there.
PART.1: What kind of...?
PART.1: There's a lot of positions,
I think there's a lot of...
PART.2: Or you can go
even to some places
that are like researchers
PART.2: and also part of industry
like Ford or things like this.
PART.1: I think that's...
PART.1: I want to search more
about these positions.
PART.1: Like if you do research,
but for industry or a company
PART.1: or something, so which companies
you think I should search maybe?
PART.2: The two that I know
PART.2: because I work in one of them
is... is quite good.
PART.1: I am working...
I am working as a Hebe.
PART.2: Hebe, ok.
PART.1: Yes, but I think
I want to work there more.
PART.1: I don't know that one,
I should look it up.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: I think I've heard about it.
PART.2: And also, I don't know if...
or something like that.
PART.1: No, not so much.
PART.1: I have no experience with them,
I've never tried it.
PART.1: Ok, let's see
if I can remember that.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: How have you got
to this experiment?
PART.1: You work for them in the city?
PART.2: No, I don't remember,
someone from UB shared it
like several months ago.
PART.1: It was in January
or some time and I signed up
at that time and...
PART.1: You forgot about it.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: But they called you later.
PART.1: Ah, interesting.
PART.2: Yes.
SUPERVISOR: Ok, now let's start!