PART.2: So like you start first
and then I go right?
PART.1: Yes, I don't know
if it is one each
or as you prefer.
PART.2: I think is more easy
if one goes first.
PART.1: Ok, then you want
to go first and guess?
PART.2: Ok.
PART.2: Is it a sea animal
or a land animal?
PART.1: It's not a yes or no question.
PART.1: You have to ask
yes or no questions.
PART.2: Ah, oj.
PART.1: You have to ask
yes or no questions.
PART.2: Is it a sea animal?
PART.1: Can you rephrase
the question a bit?
PART.2: Does this animal live in the sea?
PART.1: Like mostly or...?
PART.2: Does my animal mostly
live in the sea?
PART.1: More yes than no.
PART.2: Mostly and more yes
than no, ok.
PART.2: Does this animal
have a hard shell?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: I have already asked you two.
PART.2: More yes than no...
PART.2: Do you know these dolphins?
How do you call these dolphins
that are really smart?
PART.2: That are used in the zoo.
PART.1: Yes, I know what you mean.
PART.2: Do these dolphins
hunt this animal?
PART.1: Oh my God!
You are asking
very difficult questions!
PART.2: When do they eat?
PART.1: I wouldn't say no,
I say no.
PART.2: They are not in their menu?
PART.1: Not tipically, no.
PART.2: Does this animal live
in the cold like arctic zones
or is it like in the tropical...?
PART.2: It has to be yes or no, yes.
PART.2: Does it live in arctic places?
PART.1: Not tipically.
PART.2: Not tipically...
PART.2: Ok, so it is not
like a penguin or something like this.
PART.1: No, that was your decision
because I cannot know
what is the question.
PART.1: Ok, this is another question
that I already have five.
PART.2: It is not tropical,
it is not a turtle...
PART.2: I am thinking in my head
and I am not asking.
PART.2: It is not a turtle,
it lives in the sea
but it can also come to the land
but mostly in the sea, wow...
PART.2: Is this like a...?
PART.2: Does this animal eat fishes?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: So, it cannot be some kind of...
PART.2: It eats fishes
and it lives in the sea
and it can also be on land...
PART.2: In the sea,
it does not live in rivers?
PART.1: Why...
PART.2: Yes or no?
PART.1: It may...
PART.2: It is not a yes
or no answer but ok.
PART.1: It can, it can.
PART.1: It is not this close I would say.
PART.2: I have already a lot of questions.
PART.2: Does this...
PART.2: So, it is not a crocodile
because a crocodile don't eat fish,
I don't think so.
PART.1: It is not a crocodile.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Is it a type of fish?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: Type of snake?
PART.2: What?
PART.1: No.
PART.1: How many questions
do you have left?
PART.2: I think I am done,
I already have ten.
PART.1: You can have one more guess
I would say.
PART.2: It is not a type of fish,
not a type of snake...
PART.2: What type of animals
are there then?
PART.2: It is not a turtle, it eats fish
so it cannot be a crab,
PART.2: it lives in the sea,
it can live mostly in the sea...
PART.1: I mean, maybe you have
to fight my answers
to be honest,
PART.1: so maybe they are not bad
so maybe I am wrong
PART.1: and I didn't say
that live in the sea.
PART.1: It is like around it.
PART.2: It does not live in the sea?
PART.1: It does not specifically
sleep in the sea
if it is what you ask.
PART.2: But it eats fish
so it is like a bird.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Seagull?
PART.1: No.
PART.1: No, it is not a seagull.
PART.2: Some bird...
PART.2: Come on...
PART.2: But it eats...
I don't know, flamingos?
PART.1: No, not a flamingo.
PART.2: Is it like an animal supercommon
or is it like a rare one?
PART.1: It is pretty famous.
PART.2: You are making me
my life harder.
PART.2: Pretty famous,
a bird that eats fish
and it is pretty famous.
PART.2: It has to be a seagull...
PART.1: It has to be a seagull...
No, it is not a seagull.
PART.2: I mean, eagles don't hunt fish.
PART.1: No, I think you already passed
your ten questions.
PART.2: Maybe we start
with something I lost.
PART.1: Ok, so let's try
to do mine and maybe
you can guess yours
in the meantime.
PART.1: Am I mostly based on land?
PART.1: Not water, like a dry place.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Do I have a vertebra?
Like a spine?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Am I hairy?
PART.1: Ok, oh my God!
This is so difficult.
PART.1: There is so many options, ok.
PART.1: Am I smaller than average cats?
PART.2: Smaller than average cats...
PART.1: Just like this,
Am I smaller like this?
PART.2: I am not sure
because I didn't see this animal
but I would say no.
PART.1: So this crosses a lot of options.
PART.2: I am not sure
because I didn't see this animal
but I would say no.
PART.1: So this crosses a lot of options.
PART.2: I would say no,
but maybe I am wrong.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.1: Do I live in a hot place?
PART.1: Like I am a typically like...
PART.2: Typically a hot place?
PART.1: Like a hot, hot place.
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Ok, Jesus Christ, ok.
PART.1: So I am hairy,
I am probably bigger than a cat
PART.1: but you are not sure,
I live more on land,
PART.1: I have spine
and I don't live in a hot place.
PART.1: Now it is like
a ten thousand species left.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.1: I think I have five or six.
PART.2: Five more yes,
six for the one.
PART.1: Am I a hervibore?
PART.1: Like only eating the plants?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.1: So I am not living in a hot place,
I am not a plant eater...
PART.1: Am I a... Oh my God!
PART.1: This is so difficult.
PART.1: So I am not a plant eater...
PART.1: Ok, so I am a...
PART.1: Am I a rodent?
PART.1: Well, maybe that one is..
PART.2: Rodent like a...
PART.1: No, no, no,
forget it.
PART.2: Refresh.
PART.1: Am I a predator?
PART.2: Like can you hunt?
PART.1: Yes, do I hunt?
PART.2: Yes...?
PART.2: It is debatable,
what do you mean by hunt?
PART.2: Like catching?
PART.1: Like capture animals.
PART.2: No, I don't know.
PART.1: Do I catch living things?
PART.2: Yes, yes, yes,
the answer is yes.
PART.1: Do I catch living things?
PART.2: Yes, yes, yes,
the answer is yes.
PART.1: So I am hairy,
I am pretty big,
PART.1: I catch other things, I am living
on land, Jesus Christ!
PART.1: Do I live
in more than one continent?
PART.2: I think so, yes.
PART.2: Probably, I am not sure.
PART.1: Am I a wild animal?
PART.2: Wild?
PART.1: That seems like my last question.
PART.2: White or wild?
PART.1: Wild.
PART.1: Like "salvaje",
like living wild.
PART.2: Wild! Yes, you are wild,
definitely yes.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.1: Do I have more questions?
PART.2: Yes, you have one more.
PART.1: So you are not very clear
about being bigger than a cat,
PART.1: that makes me think
that must be something
you are not so familiar with
PART.1: but you think I live
in more than one continent.
PART.2: Yes, you have one more.
PART.1: So you are not very clear
about being bigger than a cat,
PART.1: that makes me think
that must be something
you are not so familiar with
PART.1: but you think I live
in more than one continent.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Can I fly?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: That was the last question.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Oh Jesus Christ...
PART.1: You don't know what it is,
like a...
PART.1: Not the big one,
the nutria or something like that.
PART.2: No, but... No.
PART.2: Well...
PART.1: Wow, oh my God!
This is so difficult.
PART.2: Well...
PART.1: Wow, oh my God!
This is so difficult.
PART.1: Ten questions to cover
so many species of animals
is so difficult.
PART.1: Oh my God!
I am totally lost.
PART.1: I am hairy,
I am maybe bigger than a cat,
I live in land...
PART.2: You have spine,
you can be
from different continents...
PART.1: I have spine,
I can catch animals...
PART.2: You have spine,
you can be
from different continents...
PART.2: You can catch animals.
PART.1: Am I a fox?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: No!
PART.1: It is stressed, I don't know,
you want to guess yours
once more?
PART.2: So, it is like a bird
that catches fishes
and it is not a seagull,
PART.2: I don't really have
a lot of vocabulary for birds
that hunt for fish
PART.2: but you are saying
that is supercommon
PART.1: Yes, it is quite common.
PART.2: It is quite common...
PART.1: Ducks don't eat fishes?
PART.1: No, they don't eat fish.
PART.1: Yes, but I don't know
and I don't think they...
PART.1: No, they don't eat fish.
PART.1: Yes, but I don't know
and I don't think they...
PART.2: No...
PART.2: It is not a...?
PART.1: It is not a seagull!
PART.2: Is it simnifically different
from a seagull?
PART.1: Oh, this can be a lot of things,
it is relatively different.
PART.1: In somes places
it is not that different.
PART.2: You can also keep on
asking questions,
I think we've already lost,
so we can just...
PART.1: You said that I live in the wild
but am I very dangerous?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Am I a rodant like...?
PART.2: You are not exactly a rodant.
PART.1: Do I live Europe as well?
PART.2: I am not an expert
in animals so...
PART.1: Do you think
I live in Spain?
PART.2: I am not an expert
in animals so...
PART.1: Do you think
I live in Spain?
PART.2: I think you can live
wherever you want,
PART.2: I mean, you don't need
any special requirement.
PART.1: Oh my God! Is it a racoon?
PART.2: I think you can live
wherever you want,
I mean, you don't need
any special requirement.
PART.1: Oh my God! Is it a racoon?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Anywhere I want?
Is it a dog?
PART.2: No.
PART.2: There is not plenty,
I can tell you that.
PART.1: Wow, I can live anywhere,
but I live on sea and I cannot fly
so it must be common everywhere.
PART.2: I guess you don't have
any special requirement
to live in a particular place.
PART.2: I guess you don't have
any special requirement
to live in a particular place.
PART.1: A bear?
No, that is not...
PART.2: I mean, yes...
PART.1: It must be like a cat
so it is like...
PART.1: Wow, I can live anywhere,
I am hairy,
am I brown usually?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: Am I white usually?
PART.2: Well, not fully white.
PART.2: Am I white?
PART.1: No, no.
PART.2: Am I black?
PART.1: You are like brown.
PART.1: I mean, I said you,
your animal is white.
PART.2: What??
PART.1: I mean, I said you,
your animal is white.
PART.2: My animal is white.
PART.1: Yes, your animal
is more white, yes.
PART.1: Yes, partially white.
PART.2: Is it then gaviota?
But gaviotas don't hunt fish.
PART.1: It is not gaviota, not a seagull.
PART.2: I don't know the name
of the animals that live in the sea,
I can visualize them
but I don't know their names.
PART.2: Can we start giving more clues
like which letter does it start
the name?
PART.1: Yours? P.
PART.2: Peacock?
No, peacock no.
PART.1: No... No…
PART.2: Penguin no, I said it already.
PART.2: Pidgeon no.
PART.2: Parrot no.
PART.1: No, no.
PART.2: Parrot does not eat fish.
PART.1: No.
PART.1: It's a pelican.
PART.2: A pelican...
PART.1: What letter
does my animal start?
PART.2: A.
PART.1: A in English?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: In English?
PART.2: Can I give you
a superstrong hint?
PART.1: i was hairy, so...
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: In English A...
PART.2: I mean to be more explicit
by animals I mean bugs.
PART.1: Bugs don't have a spine.
PART.2: No, I mean catching fits on...
PART.1: Ok, because it was like A
and cat is A and cat is bugs...
PART.2: No, I mean catching fits on...
PART.1: Ok, because it was like A
and cat is A and cat is bugs...
PART.1: I really hope it is not an insect.
PART.2: It catches insects, yes.
PART.1: A and it is hairy,
it catches insects...
PART.2: To be more specific,
I can be super specific.
PART.1: Ah! Anteater!
PART.2: Yes!
PART.1: And you are telling me
that can live in any continent?
And anteater?
PART.2: I don't know, I don't know.
PART.1: And you are telling me
that can live in any continent?
And anteater?
PART.2: I don't know, I don't know.
PART.1: It is like, I don't know,
maybe you are right.
PART.2: I mean, it can only eat ants
so it can be...
PART.1: It is like, I don't know,
maybe you are right.
PART.2: I mean, it can only eat ants
so it can be...
PART.2: Where is it?
In Australia or something?
PART.1: Africa maybe.
PART.2: Or Africa, I don't know.
PART.1: But trust me,
I would have never guessed it,
it is super difficult.
PART.1: Ok, let's put it off.
PART.2: A pelican, I could
picture this bird but I could not
remember the name of this.
PART.1: Yes, I mean, no offense
but this was like super difficult.
PART.1: I mean, I wouldn't have
guessed this either but this...
PART.2: I had the picture of this bird
in my head but I couldn't know
and remember the name of this.
PART.1: I think with ten questions
it is not enough
because you could have
three of four questions
on variety list
PART.1: and other three or four "is it a
mammal" or this kind of animal and
another three or four
PART.2: But with yes or no
is difficult to point this.
PART.1: I would have never
guessed this.
PART.1: Wow, oh my God!
And this is for kids?
PART.1: This is incredible,
but I love this game,
PART.1: I play this game sometimes
with posits or something similar.
PART.1: I didn't know
that can exist
in this kind of crown.
PART.2: Crown, yes...
PART.2: What we were doing
was like we were acting
like the animal and then the people
took us.
PART.1: Wow, so a pelican...
No, this could be easier
if we could act like the animal.
PART.2: This could be easier,
you just have to eat an ant
with your mouth...
PART.2: You just eat an ant
and you can find the answer well.
PART.2: For this you will need
to find a fish.
PART.1: Hmm, yes.
PART.2: Should we keep on talking?
PART.1: I don't know.
PART.1: I think he should
be coming back.