PART.1: Ok, good.
PART.1: Good, what do you prefer?
PART.2: I think one each
because you can listen
PART.2: what the other person ask
and you can be like
"ah, I could ask it too".
PART.2: Because sometimes
I am like "what should I ask?"
PART.1: Ok, good, yes.
PART.1: So, do you want to start?
PART.2: I can start,
because I have already
a question in my head
or you want to start?
PART.1: No, you can do it.
PART.2: Ok, do I live on land
or in the water?
Ok, you have to say on land.
PART.1: No, no.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: Is it a mammal?
PART.2: Mammal?
PART.1: Mammal, that eats milk
when it is young.
PART.2: Mammal?
PART.1: Mammal, that eats milk
when it is young.
PART.2: Ah, that is.
PART.2: I think so, I think so.
PART.2: Sorry, I am not a biologist.
PART.2: I think so, sorry.
PART.2: Let me get one more question
because I didn't finish so well this.
PART.1: Well, let's do another one.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: I don't know,
is it possible to see me in the zoo?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Yes, ok, good.
PART.2: Do I live in the water?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.2: There is one left
but it is one less question.
PART.1: A second question, let's see...
PART.1: Is it possible to eat?
Do people usually eat it or not?
PART.2: Usually not...
I think when it is hunted
you can eat it afterwards,
PART.2: but if it was hunted before
because of something else maybe.
PART.2: I am not sure, it is meat,
you can eat every animal?
PART.2: But it is not typical,
when I go to a restaurant
I would never eat it,
so there is not need of it.
PART.1: Ok, ok.
PART.2: Ok, so I live in the air?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: Definitely, ok?
PART.1: Let me see...
PART.1: I don't like this game.
PART.2: I have never played it
only with ten questions,
PART.2: I can usually ask
as many questions as I want,
but then it was ok.
PART.1: Yes, I mean,
I am not a good guesser.
PART.1: Let's say, in the zoo,
we don't eat it,
am I like a big animal?
PART.2: Yes, it is a big animal
for my opinion, yes,
it is bigger than me.
PART.1: Ok, good.
PART.2: I have wings?
PART.1: Yes, you do have wings.
PART.2: Ok, that one I needed
so I can go, ok.
PART.1: Ok, but you are like
getting there.
PART.2: Ok, good.
PART.1: So I am a big animal.
PART.1: I don't know,
do I live like in Africa?
PART.2: No, I don't think so,
it is not African
and you can find it in Europe a lot.
PART.2: Not a lot!
It was now not a lot anymore
but it was a lot before.
PART.1: Ok, good, ok.
PART.2: Ok, am I a bird?
PART.1: Yes
PART.2: Do I have to guess which bird?
PART.1: Well, I think so
because it is more specific.
PART.2: Ok, ok, good to know.
PART.1: It is a type of bird!
PART.2: Ok, I think
this was already a question.
PART.2: It is only ten questions,
ok, you can go then.
PART.1: Ok, so, do I probably have
different colors?
PART.2: No, it's one color what you have.
PART.1: But you can have
like different types,
I don't know,
it can be brown and white...
PART.2: Like a mixed in one?
PART.1: Or different types.
PART.2: Right now, in this picture
is like one color and I am sure
that is always this color,
PART.2: I am not sure
if in other countries is different
but no, I think it is always the same.
PART.2: Maybe some different tones
of it but one color,
quite boring yes.
PART.1: Ok, ok.
PART.2: Do I live at the sea?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: Ok, how many questions
do I really have?
PART.1: I think we are on the five no?
PART.2: Maybe, five is good.
PART.1: Yes, five,
we are like in the middle.
PART.1: Do I have like a long...
I don't want to say it, hair?
PART.1: Does it have
like long or short hair?
PART.2: What is short for you?
Long is like this?
PART.1: Yes, yes.
PART.2: When I look at the picture
I would say long.
PART.1: So it can be like... Ok, ok.
PART.2: Ok, Am I an animal in the zoo?
PART.2: You can watch me at the zoo
or is it really common in the street?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: Both not?
PART.1: Common in the street, no.
PART.2: Ok, at the zoo?
PART.2: Not really.
PART.1: It depends, it is not...
I would say yes but not common.
PART.1: It is not something like...
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: Do I live in the forest?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: I live by the sea,
I can be in the zoo
PART.2: but not common in the street,
am I also in a forest?
PART.1: Sorry?
PART.2: Am I also living in the forest?
PART.1: Yes, yes, more forest.
PART.2: So many birds...
PART.1: More like wild, you know?
PART.2: Ok, ok.
PART.1: Let me see mine,
I live in the forest...
PART.1: Do I have a tail?
PART.2: The tail is a...?
PART.2: Yes, no, you don't have.
PART.2: Maybe a small one,
I think on the back
there is a small one
but I can't see on the picture.
PART.1: But it is not like common to have.
PART.2: No, it is not like long.
PART.1: No.
PART.2: Oh God, I didn't know
what it was,
I need a picture of the back,
but I don't think so.
PART.2: It has like a small, maybe.
PART.2: Yes, maybe.
PART.1: How many questions
do I have, seven right?
PART.2: I think we have seven right now.
PART.2: But I don't know,
I think my problem
is that I don't know English words
PART.2: for all the birds
but we will see.
PART.2: Do I eat...?
PART.2: What can I eat in the forest?
Insects?
PART.1: I think so, yes.
PART.1: Yes, I mean...
PART.1: There is not one specific insect,
there is like any...
PART.2: Yes, maybe any bird
could eat insects in the forest.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: It is ok, I don't mind.
PART.1: Ok, ok.
PART.1: Ok...
PART.1: When I walk,
does it in four legs?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: Am I colorful
as I have mixed colors
or is it one color?
PART.1: You have very specific colors
and usually two.
PART.2: Ok, two colors...
PART.1: You don't see
but as a standard people
don't think other than two colors.
PART.1: Very specific colors.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.2: There are birds of two colors
which is not in the zoo?
PART.2: I have to think about it, ok.
PART.1: Ok, I know is kind of hard
but it is very...
PART.2: I have to think about it, ok.
PART.1: Ok, I know is kind of hard
but it is very...
PART.2: Once I see it I will remember.
PART.1: Ok, I know is kind of hard
but it is very...
PART.2: Once I see it I will remember.
PART.1: Yes, definitely,
but there is like specific...
PART.1: And you are getting there
and has two colors very standard.
PART.1: Of course you can find other,
but people usually remember
two specific colors.
PART.2: Two specific, for example,
in stripes or two together,
like one animal with two colors.
PART.1: Different zones, yes.
PART.2: Ah, one color and one color.
PART.1: One part of the bird in one color
and the rest of the bird
in another color.
PART.2: Ok, ok, ok,
I have maybe a guess.
PART.2: Ok, that was one really good.
PART.1: I think I see it in your smile.
PART.2: That was something, yes.
PART.1: You are getting there,
so I can walk in four...
PART.1: No, it is no this one,
I am just trying...
PART.2: Yes, sure.
PART.2: A bird can fly...
PART.1: Sorry, I am thinking out loud.
PART.2: No, I am also thinking
but I think my guess
was a little bit wrong.
PART.1: So, probably people,
like men, they go for hunt,
to hunt me.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.2: Yes, a lot.
PART.2: I am just guessing
but maybe it is wrong
PART.2: because it is flying
but is it a duck?
PART.2: Am I a duck?
PART.1: No!
PART.2: Because it has this one color
and then the other.
PART.1: Flying for you
is a very big thing.
PART.1: Flying is like...
PART.1: Definitely not a kind of duck
or something.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: Just like yo fly high... No.
PART.2: Ok...
PART.1: Maybe you need to be
a little bit more...
PART.2: Ok...
PART.1: Maybe you need to be
a little bit more...
PART.1: So, if men hunt me
and I am bigger than a man,
usually, I men hunt me...
PART.1: In some moments of the year,
do I sleep a lot?
PART.1: I am going very specific!
Very specific!
PART.2: I don't know,
let me think, just...
PART.1: I am going very specific!
Very specific!
PART.2: I don't know,
let me think, just..
PART.2: I think so...
You can get another question
because I think yes, maybe.
PART.2: I am not sure...
I don't know.
PART.1: Ok, this is fine,
you can go with you...
Ok, good, good.
PART.1: Yes, try yours now
and was it the ninth question?
PART.1: Eight or nine?
PART.2: It is nine already, yes.
PART.1: Ok, yes.
PART.2: You have a question,
because I am just guessing
PART.2: and it is not fair
telling you "maybe" is not good.
PART.1: Ok, let me see, so...
PART.1: Good for hunting...
PART.1: Hunting but no eating.
PART.1: So, I probably scare people.
PART.1: Like men, ok.
PART.2: Yes, yes.
PART.1: Good.
PART.1: PERSONA: All right,
now is a good question,
it is your turn.
PART.2: I have no more questions,
it is like...
PART.2: Am I big like a big bird?
PART.1: If you are comparing yourself
to all the birds, yes.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.1: You are big.
PART.1: Comparing to a man, no,
but comparing to all the birds,
you have a good...
PART.1: Comparing to a man, no,
but comparing to all the birds,
you have a good...
PART.2: It is like larger, ok.
PART.1: Comparing to a man, no,
but comparing to all the birds,
you have a good...
PART.2: It is like larger, ok.
PART.1: Definitely it is big
comparing to all the birds, yes.
PART.2: I have a guess
on my head now
PART.2: because next one
we have to guess I think,
PART.2: but I am not sure
about the name,
but describe yours.
PART.1: Ok, good, good.
PART.1: Ok, do you wanna try now?
PART.2: No, wait, wait.
PART.1: Last question,
my last question.
PART.2: Last question.
PART.1: Last question,
my last question.
PART.1: So, if they hunt me
and I am bad...
PART.1: I think that I have a guess.
PART.2: Ok, let's do it.
PART.1: I think...
PART.1: Is it a bear?
PART.2: Yes! Nice!
PART.2: Perfect!
PART.1: I was nervous,
I was nervous...
PART.2: It is really good.
PART.1: There you are!
PART.2: I think I won't get it.
PART.2: Is this bird
like a hunting bird
that is looking for other animals
and has its feather?
PART.2: It appear on Germany too
on this Euro.
PART.2: I am not sure
how this is called,
PART.2: it has a white head
and it is brown
and it is quite big?
PART.2: Is it this one?
PART.2: Maybe? Maybe not?
PART.1: So, you said
that has like a white head
let's say, and it's big.
PART.2: Yes and it's usually brown I think
and it has this nose
and it's looking and flying always
very high to see its victims.
PART.1: Yes, you are right!
PART.2: It is this one?
PART.1: Yes!
PART.2: What is it in English?
I don't know.
PART.1: Yes!
PART.2: What is it in English?
I don't know.
PART.1: See it, check it.
PART.2: What is it in English?
I don't know.
PART.1: See it, check it.
PART.2: Eagle! This is why...
PART.1: Is the one, right?
PART.1: You are a good guide
to help me get there.
PART.1: Is the one, right?
PART.1: You are a good guide
to help me get there.
PART.2: Nice!
PART.1: Look,
there is like white head...
PART.2: Nice!
PART.1: Look,
there is like white head...
PART.2: But it is black
and it is not brown.
PART.2: I thought it was almost brown
but this is the one.
PART.2: It is just like...
Yes, he is not the happy one.
PART.1: Is it the one right?
PART.2: It is just like...
Yes, he is not the happy one.
PART.1: No, no, definitely,
I know that hunts a lot, yes.
PART.2: Wow! We had made the guess
at the end as we should!
PART.1: Yes, definitely.
PART.2: Wow! We had made the guess
at the end as we should!
PART.1: Yes, definitely.
PART.1: How do you name it in German?
PART.2: Adler.
PART.1: Ah...
PART.2: It is very different,
but actually I don't know why
in this picture...
PART.2: It is very different,
but actually I don't know why
in this picture...
PART.1: Yes, the way that I see it
is that I remember a lot America.
PART.1: I think this kind of eagles
are in the dollars.
PART.2: Ah! Is it also in the dollar?
PART.1: Yes, dollar is also
or in the coins, I am not sure,
PART.1: I don't remember
but I remember something
with the American flag maybe...?
PART.1: American coins,
American bill
or something like that.
PART.2: I can't tell.
PART.1: Yes...
PART.2: This is really in the coins,
I think there were a lot in Germany
that they are flying
PART.2: but it cannot be hunted
I don't know for what.
PART.2: But there are a lot of animals.
PART.1: Right.