PART.1: How do you feel about this?
PART.2: It's like I never saw
this game beforeand I like it...
PART.2: And say that's a nice for kid.
PART.2: I never never saw it. Like.
PART.2: Can you start?
PART.1: Yeah. Yeah.
PART.2: OK. Good.
PART.2: So here is the chair.
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.1: You are good in this.
PART.1: NA A: No. No I'm not.
PART.1: I am worst.
PART.1: I am really the worst in this
case.
PART.1: Then...should be...
PART.1: No.
PART.1: That one.
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.1: It's for you.
PART.2: OK. Yeah, yeah yeah.
PART.2: This...
PART.1: Er. It's this...no.
PART.1: Yeah...yeah.
PART.2: It should be, right?
PART.1: It's really confusing
for me.
PART.2: It's confusing.
PART.1: This one...should be...
PART.2: the chair, no?
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.2: Let's see...
PART.1: The chair...
PART.2: I think it's the ghost
because ghost is white...
PART.1: Yeah, that's true...
PART.2: It matches...yeah.
PART.1: And you played this for
the first time?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: Here. Yes.
PART.1: It should be the mouse.
PART.2: The mouse, yeah.
PART.1: Yeah. I won.
PART.1: It's funny...
PART.2: No.
PART.2: This one.
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.1: The ghost.
PART.2: The ghost...
PART.2: Yes. The ghost.
PART.1: I'm happy. Two.
PART.1: It's the chair...I think?
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.1: I'm learning...
PART.1: It's the chair.
PART.2: No.
PART.2: The chair's there.
PART.1: The green is there.
PART.1: The mouse.
PART.2: The mouse?
PART.2: Why not the ghost?
PART.2: Well, actually not.
PART.2: It's the book.
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.2: The book is blue.
PART.2: It's gonna be the book. Yeah.
PART.1: Do you think you're
not collaborating...
PART.1: You're not competing...
you're collaborating.
PART.1: This one...
PART.2: Chair...
PART.1: The mouse...
PART.1: Why not this one?
PART.2: Ah. That's right...
PART.2: You got it.
PART.2: Coz it's right.
PART.2: I was like...why is not?
PART.2: Try it again?
PART.2: Another one?
PART.1: Yeah, why not?
PART.1: I dunno.
PART.1: It depends on the time.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: Should...
PART.2: Let's do one more then.
PART.1: This one...the ghost.
PART.1: This one...
PART.2: the chair.
PART.1: The chair.
PART.1: Yes, yes, that's right.
PART.1: This one.
PART.1: The ghost.
PART.2: The ghost.
PART.1: This one.
PART.1: Yeah. That one.
PART.1: This one. The mouse.
PART.2: The mouse.
PART.1: This one. The book.
PART.1: This one. The shirt.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.1: This one...mouse.
PART.2: Mouse.
PART.2: PERSONA A. I'm getting better...
PART.2: Yes, yes, yes...
PART.2: No?
PART.2: Yeah?
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.2: Yes, yes, yes, yes. OK.
PART.1: This one. The shirt.
PART.1: Yeah...it's OK.
PART.1: This one is...
PART.2: Yeah. yeah...Good.
PART.2: Yep.