PART.1: So, do you want first
to find the right pieces?
PART.2: Yes!
PART.1: So, do you want first
to find the right pieces?
PART.2: Yes!
PART.1: Ok, this looks
like a piece for the car.
PART.2: Yes, this thing.
PART.1: Then we need to find
another one for the same kind.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Ups, let's try and put
all the things all over the table.
PART.1: This is the other one.
PART.2: We should spread it
as much as possible
to see if we can...
PART.1: This is the other one.
PART.2: We should spread it
as much as possible
to see if we can...
PART.1: Ok, so...
PART.2: We should spread it
as much as possible
to see if we can...
PART.1: Ok, so...
PART.1: This thing.
PART.2: Wow, there's a lot of things.
PART.1: I am not sure
this one is needed.
PART.2: Do you think this is needed?
PART.1: I am not sure
this one is needed.
PART.2: Do you think this is needed?
PART.1: No.
PART.2: It doesn't look
that it is so I just put it there.
PART.1: No.
PART.2: It doesn't look
that it is so I just put it there.
PART.1: I would go for the red ones.
PART.2: It doesn't look
that it is so I just put it there.
PART.1: I would go for the red ones.
PART.2: We need the wheels.
PART.1: I think this is maybe
the bottom of the car.
PART.2: Yes...
PART.1: No, because
it does not have this color.
PART.2: Yes...
PART.1: No, because
it does not have this color.
PART.2: Are you sure
it has to match the colors
that we see or...?
PART.2: Because I'm suspecting
that this may be the base.
PART.1: Yes, but it doesn't
have a base.
PART.2: Do you see this thing,
this brown?
PART.1: Ah, you mean that,
ok, like this?
PART.2: I don't know.
PART.1: Ok, let's try to continue.
PART.2: To put things together,
so you see like there's...
PART.1: Ok, let's try to continue.
PART.2: To put things together,
so you see like there's...
PART.2: Ah, ok, I see.
PART.1: Ok, these are for the wheels.
PART.2: I think I get it
so this goes between?
PART.1: Ok, these are for the wheels.
PART.2: I think I get it
so this goes between?
PART.1: Is that for wheels, no?
PART.2: I think I get it
so this goes between?
PART.1: Is that for wheels, no?
PART.2: Yes, it is something like this.
PART.1: Ok, you're right I think.
PART.2: And then, this should be...
PART.1: This, I think, looks like...
PART.2: One in the beginning
and one should be similar...
PART.2: Ah, no! You see?
There's only one
so it has to be something like this.
PART.2: You see there's only one?
PART.1: Hmmm.
PART.1: Ok, this is
part of the nose for sure.
PART.2: Yes and it should go
from the top
PART.2: From top of this, yes.
PART.2: It should be
one more like this.
PART.1: Yes?
PART.2: There are two, cool.
PART.1: Here, here.
PART.1: Ok, so that's the nose, no?
PART.2: Yes and there's something
that goes between the nose.
PART.1: Yes, I think
that is the wheel,
that black part.
PART.2: Oh, yes, that's true,
so it will go between.
PART.2: It should go like this.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Cool.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.2: And there should be
something after this wheel.
PART.1: What do you mean after?
PART.2: After the black part.
PART.1: Ah, yes.
PART.2: But let's see.
PART.2: And the other one
will go behind I suppose?
PART.1: Maybe like this
because this looks like a wheel
like this maybe?
PART.1: Because it has like hole
for a wheel, no?
PART.2: Yes, oh, yes.
PART.1: But I am not sure,
I am just guessing.
PART.2: Looks like it.
PART.2: Let's take this off.
PART.2: The hole fits...?
PART.1: There's another one.
PART.1: I am not sure,
maybe it is wrong,
maybe it is not part of this.
PART.1: Let me see,
can I see it?
PART.1: Maybe no...
PART.1: No...
PART.2: It does not look like
there is something going
on the top of the wheel.
PART.1: Maybe there's nothing there,
maybe there's nothing there.
PART.2: It does not look like
there is something going
on the top of the wheel.
PART.1: Maybe there's nothing there,
maybe there's nothing there.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: I think there's a hole here
so I think there's something like this
but like this,
you know what I mean?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: It's on the side.
PART.1: Maybe it's...
It's on the side.
PART.1: Like this...
PART.1: But then
he wheels don't fit.
PART.2: No, I think is more like this.
PART.1: Ah, yes,
maybe you are right.
PART.2: And the wheel is here.
PART.2: We need something that...
PART.1: Yes, this, yes.
PART.2: Like this.
PART.1: This thing is so heavy, no?
PART.1: This is so heavy on my neck.
PART.1: Ok, there are the other
and there must be more of this.
PART.2: For more wheels.
PART.1: Oh, there's one more
for one more wheel.
PART.2: I will manage to put the wheels
and you can look for the rest.
PART.1: Ok, that's the fourth
that is next to you.
PART.1: Ok, so...
PART.1: I still don't understand
but it is probably this piece
in the middle, no?
PART.2: Yes, it does.
PART.1: And then
there's a small one at the back,
the red one.
PART.2: Is it the same?
PART.2: No, I think it is like
one piece and it's bend
so it should be like and edge on the...
PART.1: Ah...
PART.2: It looks like it.
PART.1: But does it need this?
PART.1: At the end of it?
PART.1: I think there is one.
PART.2: Yes or maybe could be.
PART.1: There must be another one,
no, this look.
PART.2: I am missing one piece
of the wheel and I think is this.
PART.1: I think is this one at the end.
PART.1: But I don't know,
maybe not.
PART.2: Let's try.
PART.1: No, actually it doesn't look bend,
I think you say
PART.1: because it has and it is like this
and then this is flag.
PART.2: So, you mean this red?
PART.2: I think it comes in the end
and this is this.
PART.2: So, you mean this red?
PART.2: I think it comes in the end
and this is this.
PART.1: This is this
and this has an edge on the top.
PART.1: Can I see it?
PART.1: Yes and I think no,
you are right.
PART.1: Something is not ok.
PART.1: No, it's...
PART.1: Why?
PART.2: It looks something like this.
PART.1: Maybe this?
PART.1: No, it is too short
or is it like this?
PART.1: Look and then this?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: It is.
PART.1: Ok, like this
and then there's an edge
on the top.
PART.2: Top, which is this.
PART.2: But it looks like a smaller piece,
something like this.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: But it looks like a smaller piece,
something like this.
PART.1: I think that one plus the...
PART.1: We need another one of this.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: I think something is missing.
PART.2: Could be,
is it similar no?
PART.2: Or no, we can look.
PART.1: No, it has another color.
PART.1: I think
there's something missing.
PART.1: Because we are at the front
and we can't see.
PART.2: At the front
there's a bit of confusion
because it is quiet open.
PART.1: What do you mean?
PART.2: I mean, if I put it here
so the thing that is in the middle
should be...
PART.1: Can I see it?
PART.2: I mean, if I put it here
so the thing that is in the middle
should be...
PART.1: Can I see it?
PART.1: I think it is fine
but maybe you are right
because where is this part?
PART.2: Oh, yes, this thing,
this is it.
PART.1: Let's try to put this.
PART.1: Yes, it looks like
this was like this.
PART.1: Or something is missing.
PART.2: Overlaping on the brown
and the red.
PART.1: This part is not the one
that we are using here.
PART.1: D we have anything
that looks like...?
PART.1: No.
PART.1: Yes, because it will look like this
but it is not on the right...
PART.2: Yes, do you see this is red?
PART.1: Yes, because it will look like this
but it is not on the right...
PART.2: Yes, do you see this is red?
PART.2: This is like, one second...
PART.2: Should I go?
PART.1: Oh, oh, it is bad.
PART.2: This piece...
PART.1: I think...
PART.2: This red should be
the brown one.
PART.1: Yes, there's a brown
and I think we forgot
to put the brown piece in here.
PART.1: Yes, there's a brown
and I think we forgot
to put the brown piece in here.
PART.2: Here, yes.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Brown is in the very back
so I should remove this one
and now there's a small...
PART.1: I think something
like this or this.
PART.2: Brown is in the very back
so I should remove this one
and now there's a small...
PART.1: I think something
like this or this.
PART.1: No, it is smaller.
PART.2: No, it is smaller,
it should be something like this.
PART.1: No, it is smaller.
PART.2: No, it is smaller,
it should be something like this.
PART.1: No, this, this!
PART.2: Yes, it is this, it is the same.
PART.1: Ah, ok.
PART.2: The brown goes here
and now the...
PART.1: Now the red.
PART.2: The red goes on top
of the brown and the black.
PART.1: Yes, and the black.
PART.2: The red goes on top
of the brown and the black.
PART.1: Yes, and the black.
PART.2: Ok.
PART.2: Now it makes sense.
PART.1: Maybe there's another brown
here in the middle.
PART.2: Yes, there is.
PART.1: And we put
a browner in the middle.
PART.2: Like here, like this?
PART.1: Yes, to make it even.
PART.2: Even, yes.
PART.1: No, no, I mean here.
PART.2: But...
PART.1: No?
PART.2: Do you see the brown
slightly behind the wheel?
PART.1: Yes, but do you think
there's no brown here?
PART.2: There is
and there could be a white.
PART.1: Because otherwise,
can you manage if it is like...?
PART.2: Like this?
PART.1: Yes, because now
it is too high now again no?
PART.1: This is not a line here
and there's a space
and now this higher than this one.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: So, have you seen the brown?
PART.1: This?
PART.1: No, that's not brown I think,
it is red or purple or whatever.
PART.1: Yes, it is weird.
PART.2: And these are brown
behind the wheel
and on top there is a red?
PART.1: Yes, that I think looks fine
to be honest.
PART.2: The thing is
this part is weird, yes.
PART.1: Do you think
what happens if we put one here?
PART.1: It is not aligned, right?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: What if we put another brown
in the body?
PART.2: No.
PART.1: What if we put another brown
in the body?
PART.2: Yes, that would be good.
PART.1: That doesn't look like this
but whatever...
PART.2: Yes, that would be good.
PART.1: That doesn't look like this
but whatever...
PART.2: Also there is...
PART.2: I would like to see
where the red will go.
PART.1: Yes, I don't know.
PART.1: There's one there.
PART.2: Yes, it should be aligned
like this so it means
there is a brown one
like the little one to make it.
PART.1: But this is...
PART.2: Yes, I see what happens.
PART.2: What we need is...
PART.1: I would put one smaller,
yes, this.
PART.2: This one maybe?
PART.2: And then there should be
one more smaller like this.
PART.1: This is not really...
Here, no!
PART.1: I think it is not the original plan
and there is no one smaller.
PART.1: We can improvise,
just use this.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: We can improvise,
just use this.
PART.2: Ok, now this can fit.
PART.2: Like this.
PART.2: And then the other one is here.
PART.1: I am still concerned
we can't fit anything in the middle.
PART.2: Oh, yes...
PART.1: This should be
with one more here.
PART.1: Yes, just put whatever fits.
PART.1: And then we have like this color
and looks nice.
PART.1: Like this color, let's use this.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.1: It always looks wrong!
PART.1: Let's try one,
it doesn't look good.
PART.2: If I remove one layer
then it will be even.
PART.1: Let's try one,
it doesn't look good.
PART.2: If I remove one layer
then it will be even.
PART.1: Right, ok,
we miss something like this.
PART.2: This is really hard.
PART.1: I know, do you want me
to help as I have smaller fingers?
PART.2: Right, then it would be
other brown one.
PART.2: So, now what we want is...
PART.1: Put this purple.
PART.2: Yes, maybe put only one?
PART.1: Yes, to make it even.
PART.2: And then we put...
PART.1: The purple break.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.2: There's it is, yes.
PART.2: Nice, looks more real.
PART.1: And now the green one
and this red maybe.
PART.2: Nice, looks more real.
PART.1: And now the green one
and this red maybe.
PART.2: The green goes...
Ok, here.
PART.1: And now the green one
and this red maybe.
PART.2: The green goes...
Ok, here.
PART.1: Is this?
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: And then I think this one
goes at the back,
this long one.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Where are the small edges?
PART.2: And something we...
I don't think this thing
goes below the wheels.
PART.1: No.
PART.2: This thing is the base
and we are not using the right base.
PART.1: No.
PART.2: This thing is the base
and we are not using the right base.
PART.2: It's brown,
we should remove the base
and put something else.
PART.1: Actually, maybe there is no...
PART.2: There was no base
and this brown should be
something longer.
PART.1: Although, I can like it,
do we need to exactly this
or share something together?
PART.2: Ok, so the only thing missing
is that we remove the black
and the brown thing
and we put this one.
PART.1: Although, I can like it,
do we need to exactly this
or share something together?
PART.2: Ok, so the only thing missing
is that we remove the black
and the brown thing
and we put this one.
PART.2: And then it is exactly
what they want.
PART.1: Ok, do you think?
PART.2: Yes, I think it is done.
PART.1: There is no base
and we have to restore
the whole thing.
PART.2: Yes, I think it is done.
PART.1: There is no base
and we have to restore
the whole thing.
PART.2: No, just this here.
PART.1: Are you sure?
PART.2: Yes, you will see.
PART.1: Ah, I know what you mean.
PART.1: Yes, you have to remove
that is smaller.
PART.2: This?
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: We put this in the middle?
PART.2: Ups.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: I think this one is breaking.
PART.2: It is like this
and then we put the pieces normally.
PART.2: Is it like this?
PART.1: Can I see it?
PART.1: I think so, yes,
I think so.
PART.2: We need this?
PART.1: Yes, you can...
PART.2: No!
PART.1: No? Why?
PART.2: Why do I need this?
PART.1: Yes, that's the nose.
PART.2: Yes, the nose goes here.
PART.2: This no?
PART.2: And then
the brown one goes here?
PART.1: But not brown, this one,
the purple.
PART.2: The purple?
PART.1: I think so,
if not color brown but...
PART.2: Ok, and then this thing?
PART.2: I think we have
the machine ready.
PART.1: Nice.
PART.2: This one goes up.
PART.1: Yes, but at front.
PART.2: Yes, like this?
PART.1: Ok and then this?
PART.2: This one which is...
PART.1: But still
we don't have this for the...
PART.2: The two edges, right?
This thing.
PART.1: But there's another one or not?
PART.2: Yes, there should be one more.
PART.1: I think that is here.
PART.1: Yes, cool.
PART.1: Nice! Yes!
PART.1: That's right because I have
no special vision
of what is this piece here.
PART.2: We did it perfectly,
I mean is exactly
what they show in this figure.
PART.1: Yes, I wonder how old
is this for kids or three-year-old
kids or something.
PART.2: If they follow the guide...
PART.1: Yes, I wonder how old
is this for kids or three-year-old
kids or something.
PART.2: If they follow the guide...
PART.2: Now we can check.
PART.1: Ah, we didn't follow the guide.
PART.2: No, we don't.
PART.1: I don't even realize
that was a guide.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.2: I am happy we managed
without a guide.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.1: Cool.
PART.2: We should have
extra points for this.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: We should have
extra points for this.
PART.1: Yes.
PART.1: Are we still being watched?
PART.2: Yes, like six cameras.
PART.1: Do we have to build
other things right now?
PART.2: It can be...
PART.1: We can be at the lake
and the garden.