PART.2: What do you win at the end?
PART.1: A big smile.
PART.2: Oh god.
PART.1: So should I start?
PART.2: Yeah, you go.
PART.1: Okay let's go.
PART.2: I'm too slow.
PART.1: You're good.
PART.2: Is it?
PART.1: I'm not sure. Blue or red? Ghost, bottle. Yeah, you're right.
PART.2: Oh good.
PART.1: It's yours.
PART.2: OK not me.
PART.2: Is it right?
PART.1: I think so yeah. I'm sure. Blue...
PART.2: The chair...
PART.1: The mouse. But red was not there. Oh but it's a chair. Oh! Makes sense.
PART.2: Oops okay. This is beginners luck.
PART.1: No. I'm not talented at it. I'm sure about it.
PART.1: It's OK. But you had it first I think.
PART.2: I don't know. Lt's replay.
PART.1: Let's replay. I'll make it on the side.
PART.2: Your turn. Or mine?
PART.1: It's. It's yours.
PART.2: It's mine.
PART.1: Yeah? Right?
PART.1: Because the gray and the red.
PART.2: And the book and the bottle.
PART.2: Oh wow I am surprised.
PART.2: Come on Viola.
PART.1: I'm not good at this at all. I already warned you.
PART.2: Were are you losing in the other one?
PART.1: Yes I was. I was losing, sure.
PART.1: I had a feeling the other one was giving me time. You too. Can you give me some time to get some cards so I don't lose at zero.
PART.2: My turn or your turn?
PART.1: It's now my turn.
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.2: OK let's go.
PART.2: Am I right?
PART.1: I think so because the blue or the green is there.
PART.2: The chair.
PART.1: Yeah makes sense.
PART.1: Once someone cracks it I'm like yeah that makes sense.
PART.1: Maybe this one?
PART.2: Yeah.
PART.1: You waited for me. Jesus. Oh my God. You can do it. It's like I wanted to let eou some chance but I still...
PART.2: If you just look.
PART.1: I'm super slow at this. Come on. This one, oh.
PART.2: So maybe you weren't looking.
PART.1: No it's fine I was looking.
PART.2: Okay.
PART.1: I think so yeah.
PART.2: I think so too.
PART.2: Do you want to play again?
PART.1: No! I'm not sure in my head it's like I'm seeing pardons. Patterns. Like this is green, this is red and then like OK I have to look for the book. Oh it's a ghost...
PART.1: I'm really fast with colors but the other one is really not working.
PART.2: For me I think at some point., You stop thinking about it and you start like looking at it. You just let your brain work it out and you're like OK this isn’t the same.
PART.1: I already thought I got better than before.
PART.2: Oh really?
PART.1: It was really not good and sometimes it was also intuition like OK it's not there at all.
The subject is not there but I don't know. ,
Maybe I want to feel like sure sure.
Maybe I'm just slow.
PART.2: Maybe you're very, very analytic.
PART.1: I can't tell, I have no idea for it. I have no art for it. I don't know. I don't know.
PART.2: I would go for it even if it was wrong.
PART.2: What would happen if it was wrong?
PART.1: The other one can choose.
PART.2: I have to wait for you to choose?
PART.1: Yeah.
PART.2: He didn't say that.
PART.1: I asked last time because I was also just curious. The first thing I asked.
PART.1: It's interesting that they will do a personal test afterwards. How should she behave?
PART.2: How can we help her?
PART.2: Don't we keep them for the next round?
PART.1: No, there won't be a next round. Do you want to do a second round? Do you want to see me losing?
PART.2: No but I thought there is a winner in two games.