PART.1: Do you want to try it first?
PART.2: It doesn't matter, it's ok.
PART.1: Ok, let's see.
PART.1: Is it right?
PART.1: It makes sense, right?
PART.2: Yes, it makes sense,
there is no blue
and there is no... Yes.
PART.1: It makes sense, right?
PART.2: Yes, it makes sense,
there is no blue
and there is no... Yes.
PART.1: Ok.
PART.1: No?
PART.2: I think so, yes.
PART.1: You have to play
like with your mind.
PART.2: It makes sense
because this is a book,
this is red, this is green
and the mouse is grey, sure.
PART.2: It's mind blowing for me!
PART.2: Ah! Just one!
PART.2: Ok...
PART.1: They were too close
to make it.
PART.2: Ok...
PART.1: They were too close
to make it.
PART.2: I was happy
because I've seen it.
PART.2: Ok, sure.
PART.1: Is it?
PART.1: Well, I did before
so that's why...
PART.2: But I am really bad at this.
PART.2: Yes!
PART.2: Sorry, I was going
to worry if lose to see that one.
PART.2: So it's fine red now.
PART.1: You know, I am comfortable.
PART.2: Yes.
PART.1: Yes, because the mouse is white.
PART.1: Right? It is not grey.
PART.1: Yes, ok.
PART.1: Yes, yes.
PART.1: Book?
PART.2: But was it a chair?
PART.1: No, actually monster white.
PART.2: That's right! That is why!
PART.2: But you told me now.
PART.1: No, but yes now is your turn.
PART.2: I don't know, are you sure?
Because I haven't seen it.
PART.1: No, no, it is yours,
mine was wrong.
PART.2: But I should have guessed it
and I was not sure but ok.
PART.2: It is right, ok.
PART.1: Ok, let's see...
PART.2: Ok, and now we are prepared
for those if you don't mind.
PART.1: Yes, yes.
PART.2: Well, I was wrong anyway.
PART.1: Because you were going to take...
PART.2: I wanted to take this
but no, this is the chair.
PART.1: Yes, let's see...
PART.1: Yes.
PART.2: Ok, I get it!
PART.1: I did it first
so that's why...
PART.2: But still I am not sure,
I am very challenging for me,
I am just guessing
what would you like
and then is this
because of this and this.
PART.2: But there is no greens,
there is no bottle, maybe,
but you are not like
really sure about it.
PART.1: Yes, you are like afraid
to take the decisions.
PART.1: I was waiting,
in the meantime,
PART.1: for this next session
and I was looking
on the Internet to buy it.
PART.1: To buy it for my nephew
or something.
PART.2: It is really good.
PART.1: Or for friends
hat have like children
PART.1: this is interesting,
I have never seen it.
PART.2: It is really different
from other games I've known
PART.2: but usually I am not sure
if you cover as a tactic
like we can go
through these ones maybe
PART.2: and then compare it
or go maybe what can I see
PART.1: But it is going to be like that.
PART.2: I am not sure which is better.